[{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed88"},"rt":19886,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582667,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed89"},"rt":10184,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":592965,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed8a"},"rt":72746,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665821,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed8b"},"rt":11963,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678143,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed8c"},"rt":26687,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704958,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed8e"},"rt":180923,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":890847,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed8f"},"rt":23385,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":914595,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed90"},"rt":85152,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":999861,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed91"},"rt":15388,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1015605,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed92"},"rt":62387,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1078105,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed93"},"rt":9092,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1087535,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed94"},"rt":8300,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1095938,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed95"},"rt":35012,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1131054,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed96"},"rt":40314,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1171492,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ed97"},"rt":45134,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1216736,"subject":"56LBD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1d5a54a8c2dfb00ca8c2","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"604d8f415e948938fd60b536","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eda9"},"rt":34997,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118232,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edaa"},"rt":11121,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129468,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edab"},"rt":22438,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152024,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edac"},"rt":40019,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192158,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z O O O O I I J H H U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edad"},"rt":36616,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228890,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edaf"},"rt":11135,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245028,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb0"},"rt":21140,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266281,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb1"},"rt":51423,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317871,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C B B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb2"},"rt":39216,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":357200,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I B B I B F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb3"},"rt":32683,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390041,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb4"},"rt":8577,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398735,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb5"},"rt":7186,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406034,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb6"},"rt":21395,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427598,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb7"},"rt":36625,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464350,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AM11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edb8"},"rt":57008,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521469,"subject":"YU5LG","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd05f070ea506e5fec93c4","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"6062326389195dab45d94560","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edca"},"rt":17044,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102308,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edcb"},"rt":10880,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113219,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edcc"},"rt":13387,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126636,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"7H C A C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edcd"},"rt":40834,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167499,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A 04 PMU U F F O O I J Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edce"},"rt":50286,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217821,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd0"},"rt":6953,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":227892,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"F 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd1"},"rt":17403,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245331,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd2"},"rt":38327,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283692,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G F B B B I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd3"},"rt":12657,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":296387,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd4"},"rt":49880,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346307,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd5"},"rt":12104,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358444,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd6"},"rt":6656,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365139,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd7"},"rt":54097,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":419267,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z Z F F M M M G F F C C O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd8"},"rt":27247,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446604,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"N O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edd9"},"rt":20049,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466683,"subject":"ZZ7LS","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd204c084597ea0eda3da","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610898813e48dc2864965122","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edeb"},"rt":33320,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147285,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"11 AMC 11 AMZ C 11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edec"},"rt":15718,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163067,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"D D A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eded"},"rt":15353,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178484,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C C C Z U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edee"},"rt":47667,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226213,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z 03 PM03 PM04 PMB 04 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edef"},"rt":118728,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344998,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf1"},"rt":16929,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367020,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf2"},"rt":21666,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388741,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"6F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf3"},"rt":44216,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433022,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf4"},"rt":26400,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":459478,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"X H J J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf5"},"rt":76476,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536022,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"F 02 PMF F O F F F F F F F F F F 05 PM06 PMN "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf6"},"rt":14685,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550894,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3312 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf7"},"rt":9019,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559972,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J 03 PM02 PMF F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf8"},"rt":70979,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":631008,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z 06 PMZ Z N N Z N 06 PMZ Z F Z B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edf9"},"rt":41854,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":673050,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM03 PM07 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631edfa"},"rt":15165,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":688276,"subject":"CVHEE","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd18bd61600294854844c8","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc90756b4544c0efde8d8b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee0c"},"rt":11386,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559837,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee0d"},"rt":9967,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573160,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee0e"},"rt":29865,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603257,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee0f"},"rt":16719,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622364,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee10"},"rt":38505,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661696,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee12"},"rt":8530,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":678458,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee13"},"rt":17917,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":697278,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee14"},"rt":37535,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":737005,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee15"},"rt":26882,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":777294,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"3B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee16"},"rt":32534,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":813745,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B F F 04 PMF C B 02 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee17"},"rt":15026,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":829469,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee18"},"rt":6768,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":837095,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee19"},"rt":29477,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":871411,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee1a"},"rt":25727,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":900624,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PMX M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee1b"},"rt":59073,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":961154,"subject":"8TG97","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd1cc8028870639a4844d0","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"610508c09d61c098f072605b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J","hovered":"X B F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee2d"},"rt":10523,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79775,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee2e"},"rt":10325,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90207,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"G H O O O O A A K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee2f"},"rt":10238,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100554,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C C C C 09 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee30"},"rt":96177,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196832,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM04 PMB 04 PM03 PMF F Z Z Z Z U K O O H H I I I I 09 AM01 PM02 PMJ O C 09 AM05 PME E K K K K F H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee31"},"rt":56719,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253921,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"H I 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee33"},"rt":8099,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269794,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee34"},"rt":24267,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294169,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I E B M O X 12 PM01 PMO X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee35"},"rt":71505,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365906,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"9B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee36"},"rt":48137,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414413,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J 09 AMJ J I B B 3I E E G 02 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee37"},"rt":34985,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449770,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z Z X X A F 10 AMB F M Z 02 PM02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee38"},"rt":10297,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460172,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee39"},"rt":8764,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469043,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E B F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee3a"},"rt":42640,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":511793,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G G G X N Z 02 PMB O Z Z F Z Z Z H C C G E E E E F F E E F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee3b"},"rt":26344,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538247,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMO H C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee3c"},"rt":51503,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590117,"subject":"AY72Z","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cd08a149b4a1abebf866fa","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"62cc70a97062ed494ee97360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMZ Z H G H C H H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee4e"},"rt":9274,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1412984,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee4f"},"rt":8184,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1421270,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee50"},"rt":47481,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1468858,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"1010C 10 AMC 04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PMB 05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee51"},"rt":29085,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1498051,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM03 PM703 PMC A 06 PM4I X X 08 AM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee52"},"rt":68045,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1566203,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I I 12 PMI I 11 AMI I I O I 11 AM11 AMZ O 8O 5512 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee54"},"rt":35916,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1615317,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H H G E A E G 06 PM11 AM03 PM04 PM05 PM03 PM02 PMM B B F F F F J 10 AMJ 09 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee55"},"rt":36979,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1652407,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"89B O D N N D 2D X M F F B B B F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee56"},"rt":35215,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1687708,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee57"},"rt":43852,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1731662,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O O J I B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee58"},"rt":6909,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1738680,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4F F B B M 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee59"},"rt":6629,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1745411,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J J M 02 PM01 PM12 PMF F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee5a"},"rt":12345,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1757859,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B 12 PM12 PMF F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee5b"},"rt":42468,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1800428,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"Z H H H Z Z N N 06 PM06 PMZ Z Z Z H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee5c"},"rt":17822,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1818361,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PMX X 03 PMX B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee5d"},"rt":69041,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1887514,"subject":"TQ3BM","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217d763057e91864cd7","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"59d0ec2446447f00011f0254","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"06 PM02 PMF E 01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB 03 PM11 AM10 AMF F B 04 PM07 PM04 PM03 PMZ 02 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMM M M M 5M L L M 8G C 02 PM01 PM12 PMM M M B X X B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee6f"},"rt":39029,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141630,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O O 08 AM11 AM10 AM11 AMA A A A 12 PM11 AM11 AMF 211 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee70"},"rt":11601,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153264,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PMD K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee71"},"rt":31405,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184700,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"310 AM09 AMC F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee72"},"rt":48586,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233316,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z 04 PMH H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee73"},"rt":133705,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367053,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"709 AMC I 01 PM01 PMU I I 11 AMU U 08 AM08 AM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMI A O C O O O O O O O O I I I O O C O I I O O A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee75"},"rt":40977,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":421841,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 6G G C C C C 04 PM03 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee76"},"rt":22615,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444490,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F Z Z Z F Z O F O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee77"},"rt":109601,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554119,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7F F B G B B B B B F F B G E C C C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee78"},"rt":81664,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":635870,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I E J J I E J I J J J J I J I 6J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee79"},"rt":13803,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":649751,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee7a"},"rt":12129,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661912,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"112 PMM L M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee7b"},"rt":85942,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":747881,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee7c"},"rt":16095,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":764055,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee7d"},"rt":7937,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":772024,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee7e"},"rt":55716,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":827774,"subject":"UGDSU","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd217198c873a417e4a2e","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5fc29e457497e203c3af6bb9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"E 12 PM01 PM02 PMX 2K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee90"},"rt":26590,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212329,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA A 12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee91"},"rt":23749,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236257,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U F E E G E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee92"},"rt":20466,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256854,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A C C C 10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee93"},"rt":31057,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288049,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM04 PMG 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee94"},"rt":21607,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309818,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee96"},"rt":104337,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":422209,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMJ J 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMG 08 PM04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee97"},"rt":23413,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445820,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee98"},"rt":55861,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501810,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G 2C B E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee99"},"rt":19451,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":521408,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I 3I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9a"},"rt":87274,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":608791,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":"4F F F Z F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9b"},"rt":15113,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":624060,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PMB F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9c"},"rt":7199,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631432,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9d"},"rt":42312,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":673865,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B X Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9e"},"rt":46309,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":720306,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O 03 PMO G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ee9f"},"rt":47791,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":768197,"subject":"Y9Z0T","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd20a0966032dc4609c17","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5d1d13c26ce490001692baa2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMX X 01 PMC 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb1"},"rt":13985,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205404,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb2"},"rt":140089,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345554,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"09 AM08 AMD D D D 12 PM11 AMA D D D E E 04 PM04 PMB B 04 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM11 AM11 AMD D E D D K U 12 PM12 PMD D D 88J D D D D D E H 6H E E E D D D D 8D D D D D D E E E E E U U 01 PMU E E H E E E U D D D D D E K D D D K Z D J D D D D K K K K D D D D K 12 PMK D K K 12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb3"},"rt":70772,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416543,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"H Z C C C C C 2C C C C C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb4"},"rt":264962,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":681703,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PMG B 04 PM04 PM4C A U U U U U A A F F F F K K K Z Z F F O O O O J J J I O O O O O O X X J I I B B 04 PM03 PMU F F K K Z Z A A A C O O H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb5"},"rt":210680,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892570,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,O,J,H","hovered":"77I I I I I I J J J C O J J C J O O O 03 PM03 PMA C O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb7"},"rt":24513,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":923613,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM08 AM308 AM08 AM13E G G G E E E G G E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb8"},"rt":41562,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":965238,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J I I B B I F B O O X X O O X X X 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeb9"},"rt":297972,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1263273,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B J J J B J J J J I I I J J I I I B B B E E E E G E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeba"},"rt":38582,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1302054,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I I E I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eebb"},"rt":185433,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1487549,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I F F F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eebc"},"rt":18914,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1506667,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"09 AM11 AM12 PM09 AM10 AM11 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eebd"},"rt":12405,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1519133,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eebe"},"rt":87236,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1606429,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E Z N D Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eebf"},"rt":183793,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1790425,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"402 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eec0"},"rt":107308,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1897951,"subject":"V0KWD","study":"SGC4A","session":"62cdd21832331232175efb06","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62cb7ab9939887df5ae4c784","sona_id":"5e3af922a4907231695c413e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"C C J J F M M Z 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed2"},"rt":11948,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52450,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed3"},"rt":7155,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59721,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed4"},"rt":13081,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72928,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed5"},"rt":19478,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92519,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed6"},"rt":22653,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115282,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed8"},"rt":8015,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":124621,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eed9"},"rt":14814,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":139547,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeda"},"rt":21477,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161137,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eedb"},"rt":11550,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":172800,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eedc"},"rt":15142,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188053,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eedd"},"rt":6607,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194774,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eede"},"rt":5781,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200668,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eedf"},"rt":11657,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":212448,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eee0"},"rt":20218,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232778,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eee1"},"rt":16663,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249555,"subject":"HUVEA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44476","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef3"},"rt":25310,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60683,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"7866A A O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef4"},"rt":18106,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78897,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E D D G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef5"},"rt":71833,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150832,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A Z K F F 01 PM10 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef6"},"rt":28669,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179808,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMO O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef7"},"rt":630954,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":810855,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"11 AMI C K I I I O 11 AM12 PMI I 12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM203 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eef9"},"rt":9449,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":823562,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eefa"},"rt":17121,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840791,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eefb"},"rt":56400,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":897302,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E G G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eefc"},"rt":42842,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":940262,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C F I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eefd"},"rt":104172,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1044556,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B C F B B 04 PMF F E E E E E J J 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eefe"},"rt":8083,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1053210,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631eeff"},"rt":5312,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1058623,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef00"},"rt":22546,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1081282,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"4F 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef01"},"rt":31468,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1112859,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM03 PM08 AM01 PM12 PM01 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef02"},"rt":39921,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1152892,"subject":"0EBNN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"32887","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef14"},"rt":21648,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81268,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PMA 05 PM11 AMA A 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef15"},"rt":40692,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122056,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D 04 PMB B G D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef16"},"rt":27880,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150023,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef17"},"rt":83198,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233314,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U 03 PM04 PMO 03 PM04 PME 03 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM04 PM02 PM03 PM04 PME E D D D U U U U U E E E K U J J U U F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef18"},"rt":24022,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257623,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"K H I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1a"},"rt":8047,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270910,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1b"},"rt":50121,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321118,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E E F F F F M M J J J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1c"},"rt":42752,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363956,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I B B B B E G E I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1d"},"rt":14773,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":378815,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1e"},"rt":30407,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409309,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F L H F F M Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef1f"},"rt":9085,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418482,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef20"},"rt":5049,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423619,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef21"},"rt":140023,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":563731,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z X B F B B B B F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef22"},"rt":44357,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":608373,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4L L 03 PMX X 03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef23"},"rt":3105,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":611571,"subject":"SS9C9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37334","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef35"},"rt":22158,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158137,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM9"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef36"},"rt":8637,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166925,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A E E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef37"},"rt":58989,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226127,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,U,B","hovered":"U A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef38"},"rt":24070,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250558,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef39"},"rt":41671,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292376,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef3b"},"rt":12249,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313095,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef3c"},"rt":70033,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383273,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I J J J J 01 PM12 PMI B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef3d"},"rt":44728,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428350,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef3e"},"rt":75500,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":503995,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef3f"},"rt":20312,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524766,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef40"},"rt":16393,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541369,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I 12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef41"},"rt":12611,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554120,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef42"},"rt":30332,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":584620,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef43"},"rt":46396,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631200,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef44"},"rt":12376,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":643831,"subject":"580KD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"34006","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef56"},"rt":36038,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159579,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AMA 1A A A A 11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef57"},"rt":9388,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169140,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef58"},"rt":22035,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":191343,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C 11 AM12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef59"},"rt":68720,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260237,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMA Z Z Z O O Z Z O I 01 PM02 PM01 PMH H J U U 02 PM02 PMK A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef5a"},"rt":90414,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350977,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I Z Z I I O O 03 PM03 PM02 PMO O O O F 01 PM01 PMF F O O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef5c"},"rt":12296,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":370596,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G G 6E 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef5d"},"rt":32502,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403231,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef5e"},"rt":70277,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":473649,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X 04 PMB X F B E 12 PM11 AM01 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef5f"},"rt":24770,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498736,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef60"},"rt":63193,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562080,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PMX X 10 AM11 AM12 PMB B F X X F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef61"},"rt":13922,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576329,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef62"},"rt":11925,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":588384,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef63"},"rt":31002,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":619530,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3I Z X F 12 PMB B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef64"},"rt":60762,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":680428,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X M 10 AM09 AM10 AM12 PMB M M G X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef65"},"rt":20083,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":701779,"subject":"4VP91","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39291","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"I X B 02 PMX F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef77"},"rt":14456,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34552,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"611 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef78"},"rt":6858,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41516,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef79"},"rt":13318,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":54934,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C 09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef7a"},"rt":6143,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":61183,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"501 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef7b"},"rt":9723,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71016,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef7d"},"rt":17052,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":91221,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"B 11 AM11 AM11 AMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef7e"},"rt":21496,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112866,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"E X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef7f"},"rt":40906,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153900,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"03 PM03 PM02 PMB B B 10 AMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef80"},"rt":27227,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":181250,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F J J M F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef81"},"rt":7737,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189099,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef82"},"rt":6104,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195299,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef83"},"rt":7080,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202482,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef84"},"rt":9409,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":212016,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef85"},"rt":5794,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217916,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef86"},"rt":10982,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228999,"subject":"Z707E","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42121","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef98"},"rt":14869,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100814,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef99"},"rt":11892,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112793,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef9a"},"rt":18475,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131352,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef9b"},"rt":41253,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172729,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM04 PMO O O O O I O O Z Z 12 PMZ U U U K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef9c"},"rt":56560,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229384,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O I I I I Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef9e"},"rt":7484,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241794,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631ef9f"},"rt":22170,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264050,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa0"},"rt":33438,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297575,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa1"},"rt":7129,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":304789,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa2"},"rt":22228,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327113,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B B B B F M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa3"},"rt":7254,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":334464,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa4"},"rt":4091,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338654,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa5"},"rt":24878,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":363619,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X Z O Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa6"},"rt":12448,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376154,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efa7"},"rt":39307,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415555,"subject":"QRQQ1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42086","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efb9"},"rt":95190,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176754,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efba"},"rt":14505,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":191558,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM12 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efbb"},"rt":16753,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208425,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efbc"},"rt":6782,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215311,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efbd"},"rt":15865,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231278,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efbf"},"rt":15463,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253348,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc0"},"rt":30220,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283668,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"3I F 10 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AMB B B B F X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc1"},"rt":57518,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341295,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B F C C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc2"},"rt":32656,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":374057,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J 09 AMI I I I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc3"},"rt":15607,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390039,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F F F F F E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc4"},"rt":12061,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402205,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc5"},"rt":13843,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":416151,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc6"},"rt":11102,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":427628,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"04 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc7"},"rt":7866,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435602,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efc8"},"rt":13207,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449182,"subject":"843Q3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44401","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I M X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efda"},"rt":20351,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125352,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z 11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efdb"},"rt":10093,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135851,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efdc"},"rt":10102,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146275,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efdd"},"rt":37629,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184172,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K U U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efde"},"rt":39728,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224171,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I I I I 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe0"},"rt":8229,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":239288,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"66"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe1"},"rt":15966,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":255523,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe2"},"rt":29541,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285447,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E G G I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe3"},"rt":22172,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":307892,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe4"},"rt":28689,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":336884,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z X B M X C C C C X X M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe5"},"rt":10556,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347709,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"612 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe6"},"rt":5296,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353302,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe7"},"rt":28393,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":382027,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"E Z Z Z Z F Z Z F F X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe8"},"rt":26382,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":408769,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J 11 AM603 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efe9"},"rt":31104,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440199,"subject":"ESFQC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38229","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631effb"},"rt":16684,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109398,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"02 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631effc"},"rt":25837,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135327,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D D E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631effd"},"rt":9574,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144987,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"66C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631effe"},"rt":12976,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158051,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631efff"},"rt":13665,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171805,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f001"},"rt":10561,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":186285,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f002"},"rt":23019,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209399,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f003"},"rt":61603,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271089,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"7B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f004"},"rt":13954,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":285300,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f005"},"rt":8817,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294207,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f006"},"rt":13626,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307924,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f007"},"rt":4912,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312926,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f008"},"rt":42669,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355683,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,O","hovered":"I M N N Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f009"},"rt":13707,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369477,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"12 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f00a"},"rt":11909,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381474,"subject":"8ZQ3O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42990","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f01c"},"rt":12236,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174507,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f01d"},"rt":14460,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189047,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f01e"},"rt":11380,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200500,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f01f"},"rt":12678,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213262,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f020"},"rt":52746,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266073,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f022"},"rt":19099,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":293864,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f023"},"rt":14056,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307993,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f024"},"rt":51281,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359344,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f025"},"rt":46443,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":405856,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f026"},"rt":17544,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423470,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f027"},"rt":21709,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445253,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f028"},"rt":10883,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456206,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f029"},"rt":23657,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":479927,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f02a"},"rt":38100,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":518091,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f02b"},"rt":23610,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541772,"subject":"3EXU1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"30096","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f03d"},"rt":16154,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":75286,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f03e"},"rt":10300,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85685,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f03f"},"rt":22000,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107781,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f040"},"rt":41125,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148999,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM04 PMK K 04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMC Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f041"},"rt":48819,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198067,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f043"},"rt":27989,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":228698,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f044"},"rt":9707,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238498,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f045"},"rt":12363,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250949,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"8B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f046"},"rt":14386,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":265416,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f047"},"rt":5703,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271200,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f048"},"rt":20375,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291682,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f049"},"rt":4773,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296548,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f04a"},"rt":25816,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":322449,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f04b"},"rt":15882,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338432,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f04c"},"rt":5621,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344148,"subject":"79G0L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44331","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f05e"},"rt":12852,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248822,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f05f"},"rt":10808,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259733,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z Z 12 PM12 PM01 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f060"},"rt":29500,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289348,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C C C C C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f061"},"rt":56887,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346350,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"804 PM04 PMD E E 04 PMU F C A K G G B B U 01 PMH O O O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f062"},"rt":33186,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379643,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I Z 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f064"},"rt":12244,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399561,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f065"},"rt":25880,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425548,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f066"},"rt":41788,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467440,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7L C E E E E E E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f067"},"rt":30798,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498339,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J J I I I I B 12 PM12 PMB 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f068"},"rt":18169,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516618,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"3J 12 PM03 PM04 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f069"},"rt":21438,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":538163,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f06a"},"rt":4753,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543026,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f06b"},"rt":20167,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":563303,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f06c"},"rt":16546,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":579963,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f06d"},"rt":55907,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":635971,"subject":"TMWNK","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36049","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f07f"},"rt":9417,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1077826,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f080"},"rt":9875,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1087791,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f081"},"rt":29792,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1117674,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f082"},"rt":20336,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1138105,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f083"},"rt":39631,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1177821,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"D O O 12 PM12 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f085"},"rt":12700,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1200881,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"108L C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f086"},"rt":22149,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1223120,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f087"},"rt":40523,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1263732,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B 03 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f088"},"rt":15350,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1279178,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f089"},"rt":33038,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1312305,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f08a"},"rt":12158,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1324559,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"06 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f08b"},"rt":5800,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1330449,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f08c"},"rt":27005,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1357545,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f08d"},"rt":17854,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1375487,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f08e"},"rt":48436,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1424008,"subject":"ZMHS9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44407","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a0"},"rt":9302,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60703,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AM09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a1"},"rt":17181,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78185,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"4E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a2"},"rt":26146,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104547,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a3"},"rt":17536,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122388,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"07 PM06 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a4"},"rt":3539,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126231,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a6"},"rt":11002,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":143731,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a7"},"rt":21953,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165900,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F F F F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a8"},"rt":3284,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169399,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0a9"},"rt":3254,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":172868,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0aa"},"rt":21944,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195183,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F B B F F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ab"},"rt":2909,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198700,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ac"},"rt":1968,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200901,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ad"},"rt":1780,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202931,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ae"},"rt":1524,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204718,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0af"},"rt":11331,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216267,"subject":"WTS55","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44221","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c1"},"rt":22605,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66891,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c2"},"rt":29834,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96832,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c3"},"rt":10034,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106965,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c4"},"rt":53890,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160953,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"202 PM03 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM01 PMU 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c5"},"rt":44253,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205307,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c7"},"rt":9820,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":218197,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c8"},"rt":24544,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242836,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0c9"},"rt":21744,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264683,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ca"},"rt":21382,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286171,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C J 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0cb"},"rt":20145,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306424,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0cc"},"rt":10363,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":316881,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0cd"},"rt":4225,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321205,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ce"},"rt":33329,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":354646,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0cf"},"rt":32461,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387210,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0d0"},"rt":29814,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417122,"subject":"4U8TU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36486","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e2"},"rt":37847,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111310,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"310 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AM10 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM110 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e3"},"rt":14013,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126288,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K K D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e4"},"rt":20325,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147538,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 10 AM10 AMC C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e5"},"rt":57270,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206779,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM04 PMC C C A O Z Z 12 PMZ 03 PM04 PMC U U H J I I O F F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e6"},"rt":29029,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236319,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"7I O O O O 4H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e8"},"rt":7954,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":250705,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0e9"},"rt":42644,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293595,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5F B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ea"},"rt":37672,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331817,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"L E E M 01 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0eb"},"rt":17806,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":350762,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ec"},"rt":22684,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374092,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ed"},"rt":20641,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395278,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PMB B F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ee"},"rt":11094,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407314,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM09 AM08 AMM F F B 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0ef"},"rt":34605,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442240,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"G Z 02 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMJ M 12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0f0"},"rt":17270,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460478,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f0f1"},"rt":29892,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491020,"subject":"OS47Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33184","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f103"},"rt":17228,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64823,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f104"},"rt":12136,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":77069,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f105"},"rt":17998,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":95171,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f106"},"rt":62025,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157294,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"4E H A A K H C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f107"},"rt":89339,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246933,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"H I H 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f109"},"rt":9714,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":263017,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10a"},"rt":28447,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":291586,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10b"},"rt":60787,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352473,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10c"},"rt":17152,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":369921,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10d"},"rt":74183,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444210,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z 2Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10e"},"rt":6701,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451225,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F M M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f10f"},"rt":6979,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458305,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f110"},"rt":24170,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":482573,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f111"},"rt":189315,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671992,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"H 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f112"},"rt":59694,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":732002,"subject":"TQOB1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36199","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f124"},"rt":81301,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":520465,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM11 AMA A C 10 AM11 AMA A A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f125"},"rt":9479,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":530291,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"Z 10 AM09 AMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f126"},"rt":13271,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543689,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"6C C C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f127"},"rt":11048,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554856,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f128"},"rt":17710,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572691,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"6O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12a"},"rt":16677,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":597260,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12b"},"rt":29165,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":626565,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"8C O O X X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12c"},"rt":45176,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671927,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G F F B M C O C B B G F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12d"},"rt":27163,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":699254,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C B B B I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12e"},"rt":11072,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":710449,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f12f"},"rt":17884,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":728460,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f130"},"rt":20477,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":749097,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f131"},"rt":17721,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":766950,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f132"},"rt":7471,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":774544,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M 04 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f133"},"rt":12910,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":787632,"subject":"ASKL1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44488","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f145"},"rt":73479,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155172,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"J 11 AM01 PM01 PM10 AM11 AM11 AM10 AMA A 11 AM01 PM12 PM11 AMF U U 05 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f146"},"rt":42272,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":197748,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"Z Z D 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM008 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f147"},"rt":49129,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246982,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f148"},"rt":12107,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259187,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f149"},"rt":33482,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292779,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"U I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f14b"},"rt":13563,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309811,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM02 PMJ J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f14c"},"rt":59868,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369779,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J,O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f14d"},"rt":49979,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419862,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":"B J K A L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f14e"},"rt":77850,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497811,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"F J J J J J G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f14f"},"rt":45215,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543331,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f150"},"rt":33057,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576496,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,O,X","hovered":"801 PM12 PM01 PM12 PMB 12 PM10 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f151"},"rt":41529,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":618129,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"N J 3J G G K K P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f152"},"rt":22054,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":640282,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6Z Z M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f153"},"rt":83217,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":723598,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f154"},"rt":28297,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":752212,"subject":"K4Z4R","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40751","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,N,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f166"},"rt":5040,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":23394,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,F,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f167"},"rt":3994,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":27495,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K,U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f168"},"rt":3054,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":30657,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,U,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f169"},"rt":9490,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":40274,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,F,E","hovered":"210 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f16a"},"rt":13599,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53976,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"3A 01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMZ O O I I I O 11 AM10 AM09 AMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f16c"},"rt":7348,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":62707,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,I","hovered":"209 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f16d"},"rt":1564,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64384,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f16e"},"rt":1447,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":65938,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f16f"},"rt":1600,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":67649,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f170"},"rt":1448,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69227,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f171"},"rt":2305,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71635,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f172"},"rt":1763,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73518,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f173"},"rt":1527,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":75168,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f174"},"rt":1793,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":77087,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f175"},"rt":2407,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79610,"subject":"2HCLY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f187"},"rt":27671,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":62926,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O","hovered":"11 AMA A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f188"},"rt":8176,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71258,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f189"},"rt":17054,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88461,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f18a"},"rt":7555,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96173,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f18b"},"rt":11881,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108208,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f18d"},"rt":9050,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":120848,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f18e"},"rt":25062,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":146060,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f18f"},"rt":4087,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150293,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f190"},"rt":17412,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167864,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f191"},"rt":7249,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175367,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f192"},"rt":13580,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189093,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f193"},"rt":4949,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194188,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f194"},"rt":13129,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":207473,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f195"},"rt":7333,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214951,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f196"},"rt":18370,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233463,"subject":"7BBEU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32367","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1a8"},"rt":17160,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127211,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6543111 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1a9"},"rt":9852,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137177,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1aa"},"rt":19684,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156978,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ab"},"rt":13376,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":170463,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ac"},"rt":103276,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273846,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I D 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ae"},"rt":14204,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":298129,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1af"},"rt":22437,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320678,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b0"},"rt":26645,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347430,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b1"},"rt":25688,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":373229,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b2"},"rt":33738,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407081,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b3"},"rt":12867,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420047,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"008 AM09 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b4"},"rt":7146,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427296,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b5"},"rt":40274,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":467680,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b6"},"rt":36141,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503932,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O 03 PM02 PMM 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1b7"},"rt":44712,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":548831,"subject":"4U9YG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39435","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K C 12 PM02 PM04 PM03 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1c9"},"rt":11348,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55381,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMA A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ca"},"rt":6254,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":61747,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A A K O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1cb"},"rt":22260,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84118,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1cc"},"rt":30885,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":115111,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"4Z O U U K K K F U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1cd"},"rt":64863,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180084,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PMZ I O I I I 12 PM01 PM02 PMU 02 PM03 PMA 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1cf"},"rt":6666,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":192766,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d0"},"rt":16014,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208921,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d1"},"rt":25194,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234207,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7B B I I B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d2"},"rt":12707,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247022,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d3"},"rt":25636,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272766,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F B B 12 PM12 PMF 04 PMZ Z Z O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d4"},"rt":10732,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283609,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d5"},"rt":4866,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288584,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d6"},"rt":23698,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":312390,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F Z X 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d7"},"rt":42034,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354538,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X 04 PMM M J J I X M M O O O B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1d8"},"rt":30672,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385321,"subject":"8LE2N","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J J 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ea"},"rt":13725,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78343,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMA A 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1eb"},"rt":9498,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":87957,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ec"},"rt":20930,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109009,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ed"},"rt":34596,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144162,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AMC C A A Z O O O I I O 01 PMH U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1ee"},"rt":124456,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268805,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"2I I O O O I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f0"},"rt":7815,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":281957,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM08 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f1"},"rt":19621,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301690,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f2"},"rt":27592,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329393,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L L B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f3"},"rt":19719,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":349311,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f4"},"rt":37322,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386749,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J G 12 PM05 PM05 PMZ Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f5"},"rt":9178,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396050,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f6"},"rt":7438,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403599,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f7"},"rt":23048,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":426772,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f8"},"rt":20501,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447388,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f1f9"},"rt":44082,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491625,"subject":"K8UXT","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37547","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f20b"},"rt":9583,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":31048,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"03 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMA A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f20c"},"rt":16954,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48096,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E E 01 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f20d"},"rt":20637,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68830,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"K H H C C 10 AMC C C 2C C 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f20e"},"rt":16484,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85413,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"9X 01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f20f"},"rt":16775,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102285,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":12,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,X,C,O,I,J,H,F,K,D,U,E,G,B,Z","hovered":"02 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f211"},"rt":17727,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":121729,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"08 AM01 PM02 PM02 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f212"},"rt":40191,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162013,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f213"},"rt":2726,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164829,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,I,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f214"},"rt":2839,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167762,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f215"},"rt":2872,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":170729,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f216"},"rt":4841,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175662,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f217"},"rt":8294,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184048,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B F F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f218"},"rt":21270,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":205412,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"E G X J C C C C O H Z Z Z Z Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f219"},"rt":12572,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218079,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11O 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f21a"},"rt":53323,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271496,"subject":"JG9E6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42713","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PM12 PM02 PMX 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f22c"},"rt":19561,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108886,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"U 11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f22d"},"rt":9636,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118635,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f22e"},"rt":37359,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156099,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"02 PM01 PMA C O O O Z A A A Z 09 AM11 AM12 PMZ Z A A 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f22f"},"rt":57297,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213499,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMC A A Z Z Z O O O 12 PMZ Z A I Z Z F F F F F H U U U 03 PMU U U U U H 01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f230"},"rt":130336,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343941,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O 12 PMO O I I O O I O O O I O O 02 PM03 PMU U H J H O C A A A F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f232"},"rt":23758,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":372214,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f233"},"rt":30045,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402380,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B O X X X C C N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f234"},"rt":57550,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460031,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B B B X X X B J J I I B B I 11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMM E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f235"},"rt":75019,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":535153,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"04 PM03 PM01 PMC J J J I I 09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMB J I 09 AMJ J I I I I 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f236"},"rt":21786,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":557213,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"4J J J F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f237"},"rt":11657,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":568970,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f238"},"rt":5620,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574682,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f239"},"rt":82576,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":657367,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"D N Z 12 PMJ E Z Z 04 PMZ I F F F B B B F Z O F B C X X X X M M M O B E E 11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f23a"},"rt":36057,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":693696,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X O B C G G G G B B B 112 PMB F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f23b"},"rt":108985,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":802786,"subject":"7EO1O","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41737","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C C M C 02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM02 PMM M B B B 12 PMB F F B B I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f24d"},"rt":23972,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99348,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"8911 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f24e"},"rt":9751,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109200,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f24f"},"rt":21488,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130783,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f250"},"rt":20995,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151874,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"33U E U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f251"},"rt":153358,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305329,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I I I I 03 PM06 PM07 PM02 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f253"},"rt":17622,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327473,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"I I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f254"},"rt":20905,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348472,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F B F B F F F B F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f255"},"rt":55825,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404392,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O B B B E E E X I I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f256"},"rt":60842,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":465329,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f257"},"rt":96115,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561727,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F B B B 12 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM06 PM06 PM05 PM03 PMG G C C C X X O H H E E F F B B 12 PMB F F F B 12 PM12 PMI J E E 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PMC C X X X X O O M M L X X X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f258"},"rt":8216,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570215,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f259"},"rt":8440,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":578747,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f25a"},"rt":71170,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":650012,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z G F F B B B M M E I J X H Z H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f25b"},"rt":14578,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":664875,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f25c"},"rt":98934,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":763901,"subject":"0LNDY","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44497","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"E E E 02 PM01 PM02 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f26e"},"rt":21003,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":45792,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM12 PM11 AM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f26f"},"rt":10847,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":56740,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f270"},"rt":24700,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81541,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f271"},"rt":23803,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105436,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f272"},"rt":57587,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163117,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f274"},"rt":6613,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174942,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f275"},"rt":16681,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":191718,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X I J B C 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f276"},"rt":46326,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238138,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"X H F G G B X X X M I J J I J B B B X O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f277"},"rt":1680,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":239914,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f278"},"rt":1984,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241991,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f279"},"rt":2102,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244191,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f27a"},"rt":1098,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245380,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f27b"},"rt":2544,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":248021,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f27c"},"rt":2411,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250526,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f27d"},"rt":2528,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253153,"subject":"A1O0X","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f28f"},"rt":18907,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76663,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f290"},"rt":6852,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83927,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f291"},"rt":9946,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":93967,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H C C C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f292"},"rt":34815,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128883,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U C K O O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f293"},"rt":43300,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172275,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f295"},"rt":6388,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185242,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f296"},"rt":15646,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200978,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f297"},"rt":17176,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218250,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f298"},"rt":11218,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229565,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E J B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f299"},"rt":30323,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259989,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f29a"},"rt":5485,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265583,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f29b"},"rt":4793,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270476,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f29c"},"rt":14055,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":284629,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f29d"},"rt":33702,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318422,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f29e"},"rt":26640,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345153,"subject":"SOHZA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35982","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"6X X C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b0"},"rt":13660,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133647,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b1"},"rt":9862,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143619,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b2"},"rt":11096,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154820,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b3"},"rt":49463,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204425,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"4E 12 PM04 PM03 PM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b4"},"rt":67116,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271650,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM12 PM01 PMF 01 PM02 PMZ 01 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b6"},"rt":9767,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":293494,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b7"},"rt":23470,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317069,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b8"},"rt":34258,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351434,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6F B B 05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2b9"},"rt":10191,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":361731,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2ba"},"rt":34965,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396803,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B 03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMM 04 PM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2bb"},"rt":8173,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405082,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2bc"},"rt":6318,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411504,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2bd"},"rt":12247,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423884,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2be"},"rt":21462,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445458,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2bf"},"rt":42784,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":488410,"subject":"CS6SN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40010","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PMM 02 PMX X X 02 PM02 PMM M 02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d1"},"rt":54953,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":130659,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMA 11 AM11 AMA 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d2"},"rt":13024,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143789,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d3"},"rt":21489,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165384,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"4Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d4"},"rt":39300,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204787,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"E E D 03 PM03 PM04 PME E D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d5"},"rt":112878,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317765,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I O O O O O O 05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d7"},"rt":10530,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335624,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d8"},"rt":19173,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354905,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2d9"},"rt":59626,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414636,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"77E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2da"},"rt":27148,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":441897,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2db"},"rt":99877,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541882,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F B B B B F E E E X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2dc"},"rt":10972,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553155,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2dd"},"rt":10532,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":563794,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2de"},"rt":71554,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":635454,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 04 PMF F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2df"},"rt":76478,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":712228,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMB O F F F Z Z B B X X X O B B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2e0"},"rt":69167,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":781686,"subject":"FSSG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44493","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMI X E G X X 02 PMC F F X X E G X X F F F F X X F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f2"},"rt":37132,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41682176,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f3"},"rt":30625,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41712884,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U U D E E E 04 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM10 AM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMZ G G E E 05 PME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f4"},"rt":20228,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41733197,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"I U C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f5"},"rt":50612,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41783897,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PME G G Z Z 12 PMO B B 04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f6"},"rt":31832,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41815817,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"5C I I O O I 11 AMO I I I I Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f8"},"rt":8151,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":41830560,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"26"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2f9"},"rt":42127,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41872776,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B F F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2fa"},"rt":169981,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42042843,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"L L B B I B I I 11 AMX X X B B B B 12 PM12 PMB X X X 02 PMX 01 PMX X X O 09 AM09 AMJ J 08 AMF 02 PM06 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM01 PMB X X C C 6G B B 12 PMB B B J B B B B B B B 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2fb"},"rt":75084,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":42118213,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O J 09 AM08 AM08 AMB B B B I B 08 AMJ J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2fc"},"rt":38432,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42156896,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C X O C Z N F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2fd"},"rt":30732,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42187720,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"702 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMB B F F B B B F B M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2fe"},"rt":22523,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42210324,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F F F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f2ff"},"rt":14455,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":42224864,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"I B O O Z Z Z Z H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f300"},"rt":8107,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42233054,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f301"},"rt":26601,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42259764,"subject":"JROA7","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"27072","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f313"},"rt":12320,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259561,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"111 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f314"},"rt":12756,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272445,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM01 PMD E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f315"},"rt":33495,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306038,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,X,O,I,J,H,F,K,D,U,E,G,B,Z","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f316"},"rt":66636,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":372783,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,X,C,O,I,J,H,F,K,D,U,E,Z","hovered":"04 PM04 PM203 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f317"},"rt":152391,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525455,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O I I I U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f319"},"rt":13715,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":550814,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31a"},"rt":26516,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":577435,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4Z C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31b"},"rt":97774,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":675319,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"L L F A B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31c"},"rt":21844,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":697450,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31d"},"rt":48228,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":745783,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F J F Z Z E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31e"},"rt":12161,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":758050,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J 02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f31f"},"rt":9986,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":768142,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f320"},"rt":48041,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":816290,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z B B Z X X Z Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f321"},"rt":14915,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":831313,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f322"},"rt":125656,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":957076,"subject":"NNGS8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f334"},"rt":30907,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187926,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"008 AM09 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f335"},"rt":12650,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200682,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f336"},"rt":15912,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216694,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f337"},"rt":11327,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228106,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f338"},"rt":15414,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243609,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"H J I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33a"},"rt":18103,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270701,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33b"},"rt":44052,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314860,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F C C H C F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33c"},"rt":139633,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454580,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8E B B B J J J J X J J J J J I I 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMM M E E E E E E 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PMF F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33d"},"rt":45324,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":500258,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I 10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PMJ I I E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33e"},"rt":11136,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":511495,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z B F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f33f"},"rt":8285,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":519882,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f340"},"rt":6695,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526676,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f341"},"rt":39825,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":566686,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z Z F Z B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f342"},"rt":46505,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":613288,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I I I 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMM J J I I I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f343"},"rt":32797,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":646219,"subject":"Y5XNB","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PMX X X X X 02 PMX B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f355"},"rt":28966,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190054,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f356"},"rt":17668,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207843,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f357"},"rt":19237,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227184,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f358"},"rt":68668,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295959,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C U U O F Z K K O I F 12 PMF 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f359"},"rt":194320,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490551,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I 12 PMZ Z I O O 10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f35b"},"rt":9723,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":508307,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f35c"},"rt":39369,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":547796,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f35d"},"rt":75703,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":623600,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f35e"},"rt":35944,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":659840,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f35f"},"rt":94467,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":754410,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"E 04 PMO B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f360"},"rt":15900,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":770598,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"1B B B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f361"},"rt":10197,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":780893,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f362"},"rt":31306,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":812301,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f363"},"rt":53757,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":866165,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"10 AM12 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f364"},"rt":94467,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":961286,"subject":"5EFXR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44423","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM4F B 12 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f376"},"rt":11649,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64579,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f377"},"rt":10649,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":75319,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f378"},"rt":11265,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86683,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f379"},"rt":30754,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117544,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"305 PM06 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f37a"},"rt":34768,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152406,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"7O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f37c"},"rt":6954,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":162236,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f37d"},"rt":20898,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183224,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"64"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f37e"},"rt":20650,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203983,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f37f"},"rt":8541,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":212639,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f380"},"rt":25242,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237973,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f381"},"rt":8482,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246546,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f382"},"rt":4871,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251511,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f383"},"rt":25548,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":277180,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"I B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f384"},"rt":34974,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312252,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PM12 PMM M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f385"},"rt":40015,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352357,"subject":"2B605","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39946","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMX 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f397"},"rt":21993,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71561,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f398"},"rt":8949,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":80624,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMD E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f399"},"rt":26149,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106881,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f39a"},"rt":28631,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135635,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z Z Z 04 PME K K U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f39b"},"rt":35596,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171339,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f39d"},"rt":8120,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":184025,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f39e"},"rt":46665,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230890,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J M M J X X C F B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f39f"},"rt":28429,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259475,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"P F B B B J J B E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a0"},"rt":19901,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":279488,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a1"},"rt":36806,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":316486,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F F F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a2"},"rt":11250,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327864,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a3"},"rt":5454,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333426,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a4"},"rt":55706,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389240,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z X X Z Z O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a5"},"rt":35009,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424355,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3a6"},"rt":41462,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465927,"subject":"DU06L","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38009","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3b8"},"rt":9018,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92653,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3b9"},"rt":15851,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108608,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5O D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3ba"},"rt":16312,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125023,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3bb"},"rt":30016,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155141,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A U K K 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3bc"},"rt":74379,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229620,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3be"},"rt":6209,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":238495,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3bf"},"rt":21385,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259978,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c0"},"rt":532933,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":793032,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c1"},"rt":19403,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":812708,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"5M M J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c2"},"rt":27438,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840250,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B B 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c3"},"rt":8953,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":849304,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c4"},"rt":9122,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":858529,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c5"},"rt":34779,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":893405,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c6"},"rt":81042,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":974550,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"6E 903 PM03 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3c7"},"rt":38528,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1013347,"subject":"JMOG6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33004","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3d9"},"rt":13898,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":40296,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3da"},"rt":8435,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48837,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3db"},"rt":10823,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59760,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3dc"},"rt":8027,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":67964,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3dd"},"rt":14983,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83048,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3df"},"rt":28483,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":114503,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e0"},"rt":2332,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116938,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e1"},"rt":2165,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119200,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e2"},"rt":1308,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":120607,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e3"},"rt":1970,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122679,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e4"},"rt":2637,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125420,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e5"},"rt":8700,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134220,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e6"},"rt":25844,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160167,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e7"},"rt":8332,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168601,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3e8"},"rt":2709,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171410,"subject":"2QSFF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44494","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3fa"},"rt":23307,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90945,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3fb"},"rt":10964,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101986,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G D E D D 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3fc"},"rt":25813,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127888,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"9O O C C C C C 10 AMC 10 AM11 AM12 PMZ Z 12 PMZ Z I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3fd"},"rt":28975,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156948,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AM10 AMA 11 AMA A A A 11 AM12 PMZ O O O 11 AMO O I I 01 PM02 PMU 01 PM02 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f3fe"},"rt":90758,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247796,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I O O 12 PM11 AM05 PM05 PMZ Z U B F I 03 PM03 PMK I I U 03 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f400"},"rt":7439,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270358,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f401"},"rt":15113,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285613,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f402"},"rt":38255,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323954,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f403"},"rt":37729,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":361770,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f404"},"rt":19975,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381828,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10Z Z X F F F 02 PMZ Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f405"},"rt":9241,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391157,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM01 PM12 PMB B B B F F F F B 12 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f406"},"rt":4981,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396226,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f407"},"rt":12668,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":408974,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10Z 02 PMB E E 03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f408"},"rt":29916,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438972,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E O O X O 01 PMM M 04 PM03 PM03 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f409"},"rt":19271,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458326,"subject":"K09XP","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35109","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"E E F F M X X 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f41b"},"rt":10203,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":254724,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f41c"},"rt":18399,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273297,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A A D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f41d"},"rt":7071,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280450,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f41e"},"rt":17015,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297549,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"3Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f41f"},"rt":40886,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338523,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I O O I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f421"},"rt":9081,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352178,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f422"},"rt":17300,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":369562,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f423"},"rt":54915,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424572,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"B E X X X X X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f424"},"rt":12432,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437090,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f425"},"rt":4610,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441786,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f426"},"rt":10379,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452266,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f427"},"rt":8841,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461193,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f428"},"rt":66431,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":528138,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"B X Z Z Z Z Z Z Z H H H Z Z Z Z N 07 PMN X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f429"},"rt":30998,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559370,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":"I 04 PM03 PMP E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f42a"},"rt":27895,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":587353,"subject":"OCO56","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"38739","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"4M 01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f43c"},"rt":7674,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":31619,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f43d"},"rt":2703,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34422,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f43e"},"rt":1842,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":36358,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f43f"},"rt":2103,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":38561,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f440"},"rt":1393,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":40051,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f442"},"rt":2215,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":44094,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f443"},"rt":1610,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":45796,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f444"},"rt":2638,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":48773,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f445"},"rt":1674,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":50543,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f446"},"rt":1750,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52386,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f447"},"rt":1808,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":54289,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f448"},"rt":1378,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55764,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f449"},"rt":1524,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":57385,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f44a"},"rt":1686,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59165,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f44b"},"rt":1541,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60807,"subject":"BF1FO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42804","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f45d"},"rt":45569,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":316445,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f45e"},"rt":41555,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358108,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f45f"},"rt":40392,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399117,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f460"},"rt":13830,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413045,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f461"},"rt":42396,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455548,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f463"},"rt":34723,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498040,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 01 PM12 PM10 AMJ X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f464"},"rt":96801,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":594941,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f465"},"rt":242592,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":837964,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f466"},"rt":58489,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":896876,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f467"},"rt":19914,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":916893,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f468"},"rt":20040,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":937030,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f469"},"rt":20525,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":957661,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f46a"},"rt":90032,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1047798,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PMZ 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f46b"},"rt":12566,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1060710,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f46c"},"rt":17163,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1077973,"subject":"X5UK6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28437","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f47e"},"rt":15472,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82694,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f47f"},"rt":17204,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99998,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U D E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f480"},"rt":37603,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137703,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"O C A A C C A C C A 12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f481"},"rt":30430,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168227,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U K O O O 12 PMH U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f482"},"rt":41625,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209960,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"7I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f484"},"rt":9790,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224250,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f485"},"rt":19082,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":243423,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f486"},"rt":40177,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283691,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G B B B B B E E E 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f487"},"rt":19926,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":303710,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O H H C I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f488"},"rt":33926,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337737,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B F 04 PMB X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f489"},"rt":9582,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347414,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f48a"},"rt":12100,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":359611,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f48b"},"rt":28313,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388014,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X G O O Z Z Z Z F X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f48c"},"rt":27862,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415968,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMM 12 PMB J X X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f48d"},"rt":42263,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458326,"subject":"N4XCA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42347","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"5C B F C E E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f49f"},"rt":41377,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":145909,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMF 02 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a0"},"rt":9741,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156016,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"2K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a1"},"rt":13189,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169364,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"4F G A C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a2"},"rt":11202,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180865,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"11 AM12 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a3"},"rt":25927,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206908,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a5"},"rt":18201,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231467,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a6"},"rt":30050,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261618,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F O O X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a7"},"rt":65022,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326743,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F,G,I,J","hovered":"X G G G G F J I F 5E J F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a8"},"rt":66856,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":393897,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I J J B B J E E E M M M M M I J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4a9"},"rt":8917,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403124,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4aa"},"rt":16906,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420133,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"X O 704 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ab"},"rt":14154,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":434392,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ac"},"rt":14409,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":448920,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ad"},"rt":12163,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461192,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM12 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ae"},"rt":18956,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480339,"subject":"KPV5Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42741","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c0"},"rt":15066,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88911,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"03 PM02 PMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c1"},"rt":13460,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102475,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c2"},"rt":33908,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136636,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A A C C C C C A A Z Z Z C C A 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c3"},"rt":87157,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223907,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U K K K O K G 05 PMA U U 01 PM12 PMZ F 01 PMI I H H H O O K K 05 PMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c4"},"rt":96624,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320839,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 03 PM03 PMA A A F F Z K K K U U 6F O O O K K O U K H E E E 04 PME E I J D 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c6"},"rt":11558,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":337034,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c7"},"rt":17613,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354765,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5F F B B 12 PM5F B B 12 PM12 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c8"},"rt":37711,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392602,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"47B B B B X X G I J E B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4c9"},"rt":25460,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":418284,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ca"},"rt":17254,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435650,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"E F F I B B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4cb"},"rt":13049,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448816,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PMM M M 01 PMB B F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4cc"},"rt":7122,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456050,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4cd"},"rt":31527,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487695,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z B B B B O O X X C C C F Z Z Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ce"},"rt":63850,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":551714,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMM 03 PM03 PMO B O I B J J B F F Z Z E B O 03 PM03 PMM X O O I J B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4cf"},"rt":63561,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":615610,"subject":"4YH6D","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40883","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 02 PMM B B B B B O B B B 02 PMF F X X X X X F F X 02 PMM E E G G X X F E E G G G G C B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e1"},"rt":31841,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":104610,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O F 610 AM11 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e2"},"rt":29148,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133877,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e3"},"rt":60221,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194214,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e4"},"rt":5925,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200439,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e5"},"rt":2719,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203266,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e7"},"rt":12367,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":217603,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e8"},"rt":20162,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237876,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H,I,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4e9"},"rt":23076,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261067,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":7,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F,H,M,P,Z,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ea"},"rt":2608,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":263798,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4eb"},"rt":2138,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266063,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ec"},"rt":4249,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270420,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ed"},"rt":7262,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277792,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ee"},"rt":16320,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":294218,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4ef"},"rt":2927,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297256,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f4f0"},"rt":2569,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299937,"subject":"OFD35","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41267","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f502"},"rt":41547,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377661,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1511 AMA A C 303 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM11 AM11 AMC C A 011 AM11 AM11 AMA A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f503"},"rt":9822,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387560,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM02 PM02 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f504"},"rt":18020,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405652,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A A 11 AMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f505"},"rt":170035,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":575758,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM04 PMU Z 02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMH H H H B B 04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMU 04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMD D K U U K X J J 34501 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AMX X X X 02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMH H O 02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM04 PM04 PME E K U U J H F F Z A O O O I O O I I A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f506"},"rt":69611,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645582,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I I 12 PM12 PMO I I I I I I I 12 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMU U U 03 PMK H H J H H 01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMF F O 12 PM11 AMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f508"},"rt":13867,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":664999,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f509"},"rt":26672,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":691746,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PMM M M 12 PM12 PMB F F F F B F B B B F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50a"},"rt":40206,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":732025,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G,M","hovered":"X X X F B M X X B B B F M M M G M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50b"},"rt":31738,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":763836,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G G G C 02 PMZ J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50c"},"rt":55662,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":819588,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"2F 12 PM12 PMB 04 PM03 PM03 PMX X F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50d"},"rt":10570,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":830234,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM01 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50e"},"rt":9784,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840091,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f50f"},"rt":27849,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":868012,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"02 PMZ Z O 04 PM04 PMO O C X X X X 09 AM10 AM05 PM04 PM04 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f510"},"rt":18149,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":886233,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f511"},"rt":57415,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":943736,"subject":"NQHXO","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"38867","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM04 PM03 PMM 03 PM02 PMM B F B E 08 AM10 AMI F 05 PMB A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f523"},"rt":15977,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68207,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f524"},"rt":15086,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83503,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"604 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f525"},"rt":15614,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99385,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C A Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f526"},"rt":151289,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250821,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F,U","hovered":"10 AM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMU C 02 PMF 12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PMF O O O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f527"},"rt":81928,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333318,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I O O A O I I 01 PM12 PM09 AM10 AMI O O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f529"},"rt":8846,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":347981,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52a"},"rt":40002,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388133,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52b"},"rt":25203,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413531,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E C C E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52c"},"rt":17364,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":431063,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E O J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52d"},"rt":74203,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505428,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"5F F F 2B F M B B F F F B B B 12 PM01 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52e"},"rt":9659,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515678,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f52f"},"rt":15038,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531144,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f530"},"rt":50060,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":581360,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"6O 11 AM11 AM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM11 AM10 AM11 AMF I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f531"},"rt":33526,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":615043,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"04 PM03 PMM I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f532"},"rt":84433,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":699626,"subject":"VWDEZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44480","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B B B O J M X B 12 PM12 PMB B E I I E E G G E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f544"},"rt":46760,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79390,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f545"},"rt":13909,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":93415,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PM01 PMO D D D D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f546"},"rt":30702,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124229,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"4J X X J C A C C 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f547"},"rt":27238,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151575,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,U","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f548"},"rt":23393,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175074,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54a"},"rt":12918,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":193895,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54b"},"rt":43071,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237074,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":8,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C,D,F,H,I,J,M,N,O,Z,X","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54c"},"rt":27758,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264952,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54d"},"rt":26872,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291931,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"F F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54e"},"rt":46971,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339007,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f54f"},"rt":15155,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354269,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f550"},"rt":11012,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365392,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f551"},"rt":23479,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388978,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f552"},"rt":17841,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406927,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"12 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f553"},"rt":3250,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410287,"subject":"UE9PN","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44470","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f565"},"rt":35411,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82398,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f566"},"rt":15840,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98361,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f567"},"rt":12109,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110579,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f568"},"rt":11735,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122437,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f569"},"rt":15610,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138155,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f56b"},"rt":12585,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":154974,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f56c"},"rt":12653,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167744,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"55"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f56d"},"rt":9489,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177779,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f56e"},"rt":10800,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":188715,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f56f"},"rt":6057,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194880,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f570"},"rt":11048,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206053,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f571"},"rt":3826,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":210204,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f572"},"rt":23246,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233684,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f573"},"rt":18199,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251989,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f574"},"rt":13999,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266097,"subject":"H50MQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f586"},"rt":29483,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":175498,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A 11 AM03 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM11 AM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f587"},"rt":10075,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185685,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"03 PME H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f588"},"rt":19851,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205816,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C 01 PM01 PM12 PMZ Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f589"},"rt":8258,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214351,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f58a"},"rt":124233,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338689,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O I I O O O I 06 PM06 PME 04 PM04 PMK K U U 407 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f58c"},"rt":9066,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":353125,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f58d"},"rt":13260,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366490,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f58e"},"rt":43765,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410363,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F F B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f58f"},"rt":13450,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423923,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f590"},"rt":22397,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446428,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f591"},"rt":21218,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467758,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f592"},"rt":7145,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":475011,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f593"},"rt":25997,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":501116,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f594"},"rt":64209,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565440,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f595"},"rt":73213,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":638947,"subject":"NKZHC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41876","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AM02 PM3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5a7"},"rt":13109,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76565,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMZ Z 09 AM09 AMO O 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5a8"},"rt":8868,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":85528,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5a9"},"rt":11339,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96969,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"3C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5aa"},"rt":14216,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111274,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ab"},"rt":10546,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":121909,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ad"},"rt":15777,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141295,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM6E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ae"},"rt":40594,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181985,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,D,F,I,J,M,N,O,Z,X","hovered":"C H B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5af"},"rt":21991,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204070,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b0"},"rt":17175,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":221342,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b1"},"rt":618,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":222048,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b2"},"rt":10163,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232303,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"312 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b3"},"rt":7720,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240113,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b4"},"rt":15960,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256163,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b5"},"rt":8382,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264636,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 08 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5b6"},"rt":19242,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":283969,"subject":"ACYOW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41185","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5c8"},"rt":10843,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":56867,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5c9"},"rt":16436,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73675,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,K","hovered":"F K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ca"},"rt":19265,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":94234,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5cb"},"rt":12991,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108555,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5cc"},"rt":22881,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131788,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ce"},"rt":12534,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":149914,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5cf"},"rt":15433,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165788,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d0"},"rt":20573,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":186786,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d1"},"rt":1804,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190014,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d2"},"rt":5072,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195429,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d3"},"rt":13033,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208812,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d4"},"rt":9322,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219550,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d5"},"rt":13851,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233757,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d6"},"rt":13160,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247276,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5d7"},"rt":3170,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250789,"subject":"UGHBL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44505","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5e9"},"rt":15304,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":56756,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2610 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ea"},"rt":12076,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68988,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5eb"},"rt":39678,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109099,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ec"},"rt":53626,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163524,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ed"},"rt":28456,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192108,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5ef"},"rt":5403,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":200288,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f0"},"rt":15818,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216651,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f1"},"rt":32163,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249063,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"G G C C C C C X X X X C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f2"},"rt":40464,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":292140,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f3"},"rt":10773,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303211,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"J M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f4"},"rt":9056,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312834,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f5"},"rt":11947,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325544,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f6"},"rt":43032,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":368691,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f7"},"rt":23299,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392143,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f5f8"},"rt":39479,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431795,"subject":"9Y8G1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"34232","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X X J 01 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f60a"},"rt":47736,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261259,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AMA A A A A A 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f60b"},"rt":16306,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277714,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PM01 PMD E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f60c"},"rt":34208,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312066,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"11C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f60d"},"rt":68248,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":380454,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM03 PM12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM04 PM12 PMJ O O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f60e"},"rt":61806,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":442648,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f610"},"rt":10032,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460843,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"A 76G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f611"},"rt":23234,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":484205,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f612"},"rt":100021,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":584357,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L L L E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f613"},"rt":3016,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":587772,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f614"},"rt":94460,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":682372,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z M F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f615"},"rt":12884,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":695697,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f616"},"rt":11592,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":707438,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f617"},"rt":29572,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":737154,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f618"},"rt":30451,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767748,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f619"},"rt":61422,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":829314,"subject":"X2SF6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39769","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X 02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f62b"},"rt":21366,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135329,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMC 5A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f62c"},"rt":15285,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150761,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f62d"},"rt":27129,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178086,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C Z Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f62e"},"rt":84320,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262550,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMU U C 08 AM09 AMC A U Z Z O F F F U U U C A O O O O 12 PM01 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f62f"},"rt":63267,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326062,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f631"},"rt":14356,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":353853,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f632"},"rt":35543,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389476,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C C F B F B B B B F B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f633"},"rt":77801,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467359,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G E E G G B B J F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f634"},"rt":31479,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":499075,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J J J I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f635"},"rt":130098,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":629256,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O O F Z Z Z F G F Z Z Z F B B B B F F C X Z Z Z 08 AMJ B I I B B 2Z F G Z Z G G A B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f636"},"rt":12482,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":641976,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J 02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f637"},"rt":8393,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":650451,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f638"},"rt":41475,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":692007,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z B O O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f639"},"rt":71547,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":763633,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMO X B Z E G G 03 PM03 PMO O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f63a"},"rt":86983,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":850865,"subject":"A0KHZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44402","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X X X B B 02 PMX X B B M M 01 PM02 PMX X G G C C 02 PM02 PMX C X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f64c"},"rt":2957,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24653,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f64d"},"rt":2396,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":27166,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f64e"},"rt":749,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":28010,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f64f"},"rt":4936,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":33034,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f650"},"rt":2734,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35867,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f652"},"rt":2463,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":39912,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f653"},"rt":1220,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41220,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f654"},"rt":2037,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43349,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f655"},"rt":1539,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":44984,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f656"},"rt":1458,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":46543,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f657"},"rt":1256,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":47886,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f658"},"rt":1904,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":49877,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f659"},"rt":2870,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":52835,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f65a"},"rt":3016,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55942,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f65b"},"rt":3181,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59262,"subject":"12W8Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42253","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f66d"},"rt":34783,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92904,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM211 AM11 AMA A 11 AMA A 4208 AM10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f66e"},"rt":13933,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":106948,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F U D D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f66f"},"rt":40125,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147189,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"C C C C A U C A C A C C C C A U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f670"},"rt":35185,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182481,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f671"},"rt":20117,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202701,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"8A A Z Z I I O O F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f673"},"rt":45768,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":252952,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J I I J I E G G 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f674"},"rt":61211,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314276,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"F F F J J X C F F Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f675"},"rt":96261,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410899,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O L L X X B B 5B B B B X X J M I I B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f676"},"rt":85097,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":496336,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J M M J I I 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f677"},"rt":35005,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531677,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,J","hovered":"F F F B F B B J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f678"},"rt":76140,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607924,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M M B B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f679"},"rt":7227,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":615445,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f67a"},"rt":109575,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":725131,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"C Z F 04 PMZ Z Z E E 11 AME 10 AMJ J J 01 PM12 PMF B B 01 PMM M Z B B G G G G E E E 11 AMF F B B 01 PMX X X 02 PMX 03 PMO O N X J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f67b"},"rt":534658,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1260162,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"I I I I I I I B B 12 PM12 PMF I 02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB B B B B B B O X M J J J E G C C F Z O 03 PM01 PMM 03 PM03 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f67c"},"rt":130653,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1391162,"subject":"L3U0P","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39124","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J J 02 PMM M M M J I B B B O X X K K 02 PMP P B I I F X C F I I J J E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f68e"},"rt":13087,"condition":"113","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":38814,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f68f"},"rt":10101,"condition":"113","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":49031,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f690"},"rt":10660,"condition":"113","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59802,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f691"},"rt":9632,"condition":"113","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69541,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f692"},"rt":22807,"condition":"113","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92463,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f694"},"rt":14342,"condition":"113","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":108471,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f695"},"rt":10679,"condition":"113","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119267,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f696"},"rt":18655,"condition":"113","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138034,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"G G B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f697"},"rt":21917,"condition":"113","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160077,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f698"},"rt":34372,"condition":"113","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194559,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F 02 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f699"},"rt":14327,"condition":"113","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208999,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f69a"},"rt":6078,"condition":"113","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215193,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f69b"},"rt":26599,"condition":"113","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":241904,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f69c"},"rt":5618,"condition":"113","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247637,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f69d"},"rt":18658,"condition":"113","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266420,"subject":"ZSZE0","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM01 PMM F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6af"},"rt":26804,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":61591,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b0"},"rt":8441,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70134,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"G K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b1"},"rt":33278,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":103511,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F K C C K K 03 PM02 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b2"},"rt":18622,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122251,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,D","hovered":"E D E E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b3"},"rt":54982,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177329,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C C U I O U U 02 PM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A 11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b5"},"rt":14579,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":196345,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b6"},"rt":34876,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231322,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"4C C H H H O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b7"},"rt":32670,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264090,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I I J B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b8"},"rt":27645,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291835,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I J B 02 PMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6b9"},"rt":9854,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301787,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6ba"},"rt":13958,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315843,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6bb"},"rt":12414,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328355,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2B F G G 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6bc"},"rt":8666,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":337115,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M X X Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6bd"},"rt":10645,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347860,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM09 AM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6be"},"rt":10743,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358708,"subject":"2X99M","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44443","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d0"},"rt":2945,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":20572,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d1"},"rt":1336,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":22005,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d2"},"rt":1489,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":23587,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d3"},"rt":1291,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":25003,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d4"},"rt":1742,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":26838,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d6"},"rt":1480,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":29388,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d7"},"rt":3228,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":32839,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d8"},"rt":1340,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34288,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6d9"},"rt":1358,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":35738,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6da"},"rt":1426,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":37438,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6db"},"rt":2220,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":39753,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6dc"},"rt":3659,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43505,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6dd"},"rt":2069,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":45705,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6de"},"rt":1821,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":47622,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6df"},"rt":1606,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":49321,"subject":"NJFJ9","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44507","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f1"},"rt":11914,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":53992,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f2"},"rt":10413,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64544,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f3"},"rt":13791,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78482,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f4"},"rt":22937,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101729,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f5"},"rt":25354,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127217,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f7"},"rt":11812,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":142398,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f8"},"rt":15232,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157758,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6f9"},"rt":21305,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179236,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6fa"},"rt":28237,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":207605,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6fb"},"rt":67085,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274819,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6fc"},"rt":105807,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381047,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6fd"},"rt":4697,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386185,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6fe"},"rt":14427,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":400764,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z X X F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f6ff"},"rt":27315,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428226,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM11 AM02 PMM M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f700"},"rt":32166,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460528,"subject":"3R0RW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM01 PM02 PM02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f712"},"rt":96011,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149429,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A 11 AMA A A A A A 12 PM12 PMA A A A A 10 AM10 AM11 AMA A A 11 AMF Z Z Z Z Z A A 12 PMO C 10 AM11 AMA A A 11 AMF 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM06 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PMZ A A A 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f713"},"rt":17918,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167657,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E D D D K K D D D E E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f714"},"rt":20655,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188415,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C 11 AM11 AM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f715"},"rt":25038,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213560,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PME K U Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f716"},"rt":49103,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262766,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O I I I I I O O O O I I I O 03 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f718"},"rt":15152,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":280366,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"66E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f719"},"rt":27597,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308070,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"Z Z F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71a"},"rt":26550,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":334724,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B B E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71b"},"rt":27499,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":362329,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F F J J J I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71c"},"rt":19968,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382422,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71d"},"rt":10027,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392565,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71e"},"rt":13940,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406612,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f71f"},"rt":40521,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":447238,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O Z Z Z 04 PMZ Z Z Z Z Z 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f720"},"rt":19718,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467061,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X J I 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f721"},"rt":39550,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506716,"subject":"KZ2V2","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"39904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PMM B B B 12 PMX X F F Z Z X X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f733"},"rt":21171,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128945,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f734"},"rt":9581,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138627,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f735"},"rt":22115,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160842,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f736"},"rt":138558,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299492,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U U U E E Z O F F O O F F 01 PMF F F F U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f737"},"rt":209297,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":509060,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z 10 AMA A I O I O O H F U I O 11 AMC C A O O F F F F H H H 01 PMH K K U U 24I 11 AMC C C 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMA 11 AMO 12 PMZ F F 01 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMK K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f739"},"rt":9752,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":524095,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73a"},"rt":24538,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":548725,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73b"},"rt":112297,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661242,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G B M X X O C G B B B E E 11 AM11 AMJ J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73c"},"rt":32938,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":694775,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z J J I 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73d"},"rt":69046,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":763910,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F B B F F F B F F X X 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73e"},"rt":9847,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":774025,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f73f"},"rt":6586,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":780705,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f740"},"rt":64389,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":845177,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z 04 PMB B F F 12 PM01 PMX 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f741"},"rt":41861,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":887311,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMB B B B B 11 AM11 AM10 AM10 AMJ 10 AM10 AMJ J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f742"},"rt":29557,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":916959,"subject":"0X2GC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37125","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J M J J J 11 AM12 PMM 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f754"},"rt":43330,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92452,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 01 PM12 PM01 PMB 11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AMC 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f755"},"rt":7399,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99984,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f756"},"rt":11728,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111843,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f757"},"rt":5474,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":117422,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f758"},"rt":9735,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":127285,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75a"},"rt":7232,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":140105,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75b"},"rt":16752,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":156986,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75c"},"rt":41710,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198804,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G L M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75d"},"rt":24658,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":223593,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J I B 02 PM01 PMM B B 10 AMJ J 09 AME E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75e"},"rt":6403,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230126,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f75f"},"rt":9398,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239629,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f760"},"rt":5411,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245186,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f761"},"rt":10093,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255389,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f762"},"rt":13301,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268821,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f763"},"rt":9421,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278370,"subject":"YQTO6","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42169","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f775"},"rt":5356,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":36409,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f776"},"rt":4624,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":41417,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f777"},"rt":8154,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":49670,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f778"},"rt":3138,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":52933,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f779"},"rt":2944,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55996,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f77b"},"rt":2015,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":60459,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f77c"},"rt":3928,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64486,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f77d"},"rt":1926,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66506,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f77e"},"rt":2144,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":69022,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f77f"},"rt":3169,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72291,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f780"},"rt":1653,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":74050,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f781"},"rt":2537,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76954,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f782"},"rt":2267,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":79314,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f783"},"rt":1944,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81351,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f784"},"rt":1694,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":83146,"subject":"55ZBV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"35996","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f796"},"rt":12458,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":51658,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f797"},"rt":5484,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58644,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f798"},"rt":22310,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81491,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f799"},"rt":14684,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96309,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f79a"},"rt":9331,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105757,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f79c"},"rt":14012,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":128840,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f79d"},"rt":21700,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150724,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.6666666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F,I,O,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f79e"},"rt":34546,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185391,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,E,F,G,H,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f79f"},"rt":27556,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":213074,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a0"},"rt":9831,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223007,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a1"},"rt":11197,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234306,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a2"},"rt":11282,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245691,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a3"},"rt":24779,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270608,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a4"},"rt":9649,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280357,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7a5"},"rt":7835,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288290,"subject":"NR0YH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43417","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7b7"},"rt":6454,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":27490,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7b8"},"rt":6776,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34376,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7b9"},"rt":11621,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":46103,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 10 AM12 PMZ Z O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7ba"},"rt":21573,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":67785,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM03 PMU 3O H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7bb"},"rt":31300,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99190,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I Z Z Z O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7bd"},"rt":6401,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":107279,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7be"},"rt":22266,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129649,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"H F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7bf"},"rt":41359,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171118,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L B I E I J E J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c0"},"rt":8511,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":179770,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c1"},"rt":5063,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":184946,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c2"},"rt":9311,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194407,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c3"},"rt":5746,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200250,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c4"},"rt":5086,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":205437,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c5"},"rt":13100,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218644,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7c6"},"rt":4867,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223606,"subject":"7TAE8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7d8"},"rt":24430,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88541,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"14X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7d9"},"rt":7815,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":96464,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7da"},"rt":9412,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":105980,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7db"},"rt":10513,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116598,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7dc"},"rt":18438,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135140,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7de"},"rt":11166,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":153019,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7df"},"rt":18179,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171301,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e0"},"rt":60054,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231462,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e1"},"rt":11483,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243265,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"53"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e2"},"rt":27726,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271098,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e3"},"rt":6956,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278158,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e4"},"rt":7089,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285349,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e5"},"rt":7959,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":293407,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e6"},"rt":8328,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301856,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"09 AM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7e7"},"rt":15912,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317878,"subject":"T6871","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32196","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X 02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7f9"},"rt":9479,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":32521,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7fa"},"rt":10514,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":43120,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7fb"},"rt":12146,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55352,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7fc"},"rt":26943,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82379,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"03 PM04 PMK 04 PMZ C A F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7fd"},"rt":20064,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102529,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f7ff"},"rt":6549,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":111337,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f800"},"rt":13269,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124689,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f801"},"rt":62285,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187059,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"X N X J J J B 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f802"},"rt":88702,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":276075,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f803"},"rt":15942,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292258,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":"F F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f804"},"rt":10190,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302530,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f805"},"rt":4661,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307275,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f806"},"rt":16151,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":323507,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f807"},"rt":14462,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338050,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f808"},"rt":4678,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342810,"subject":"VLS93","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40355","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f81a"},"rt":13490,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":61631,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f81b"},"rt":9469,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71196,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f81c"},"rt":40672,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111962,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A Z J U D D C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f81d"},"rt":21855,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133912,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f81e"},"rt":28144,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162149,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,J,H,D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f820"},"rt":7597,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":171061,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f821"},"rt":27394,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198546,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,D,F,I,J,M,N,O,Z,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f822"},"rt":10655,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209294,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f823"},"rt":15522,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224911,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f824"},"rt":18999,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244011,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f825"},"rt":7721,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251829,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f826"},"rt":4685,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256607,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f827"},"rt":50881,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":307576,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f828"},"rt":20744,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328410,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f829"},"rt":16154,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344744,"subject":"V7HN8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44559","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,F","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f83b"},"rt":30712,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150031,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"7A 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f83c"},"rt":18855,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168997,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A K D E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f83d"},"rt":45285,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214388,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f83e"},"rt":58137,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272665,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C A A Z F F O O 11 AMO I U U B B B U U H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f83f"},"rt":65701,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338479,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"2A I I I I A A Z F O F U A U U U H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f841"},"rt":15138,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":361863,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J J J E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f842"},"rt":27029,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388992,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f843"},"rt":50073,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439172,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G B E F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f844"},"rt":28373,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":467672,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f845"},"rt":37354,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":505148,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F J J M M M X X X J B B F E G Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f846"},"rt":10675,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515940,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f847"},"rt":15489,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531536,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f848"},"rt":20835,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":552484,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z B B B B F X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f849"},"rt":22353,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":575017,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E B B F E 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f84a"},"rt":42880,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":618077,"subject":"ALCUU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"28610","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M M M X X I B B 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f85c"},"rt":10981,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73957,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f85d"},"rt":10773,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84831,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f85e"},"rt":40023,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124950,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2C C A C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f85f"},"rt":16551,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141596,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f860"},"rt":42210,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183904,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f862"},"rt":9808,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":199661,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f863"},"rt":27902,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227656,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f864"},"rt":64360,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292113,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,E,F","hovered":"4E B B F G O O X X C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f865"},"rt":20911,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313309,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"5C J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f866"},"rt":47327,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360734,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"4B F Z O M M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f867"},"rt":9760,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370598,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f868"},"rt":4854,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375548,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f869"},"rt":39056,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414703,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f86a"},"rt":25489,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440292,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f86b"},"rt":26396,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466789,"subject":"P278H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42515","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f87d"},"rt":19981,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247328,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f87e"},"rt":14167,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261872,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f87f"},"rt":20240,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":282208,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f880"},"rt":102093,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384633,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K K U U X J J J H H H F F F F F Z Z Z Z A A A I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f881"},"rt":91085,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476414,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O O O 02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f883"},"rt":11000,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":598971,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f884"},"rt":12746,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":611833,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f885"},"rt":33803,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645905,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f886"},"rt":26449,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":672847,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B B B O 03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f887"},"rt":64055,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":737079,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F F Z Z C C X B B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f888"},"rt":9551,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":747151,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"412 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f889"},"rt":14959,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":762433,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f88a"},"rt":31471,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":794153,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z X X X B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f88b"},"rt":74009,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":868309,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"54404 PM03 PMX B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f88c"},"rt":46498,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":915143,"subject":"9RVJW","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36215","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMM X B B B B F 4I G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f89e"},"rt":26732,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101584,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"811 AM10 AM11 AMA 11 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f89f"},"rt":12249,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":113996,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a0"},"rt":165985,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280201,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"K F A 43C 11 AM10 AM11 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a1"},"rt":33672,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314263,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a2"},"rt":102640,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417063,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I O O 02 PMG 02 PM02 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a4"},"rt":46973,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":474957,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a5"},"rt":18069,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493212,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a6"},"rt":89005,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582364,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"M B 4B B M J J J I I X B B E X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a7"},"rt":34180,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":616904,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a8"},"rt":32708,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":649756,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B 12 PM05 PM04 PM04 PMO 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8a9"},"rt":152311,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":802198,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8aa"},"rt":20771,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":823354,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ab"},"rt":34199,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":857720,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z B B B B O X X E G G C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ac"},"rt":15946,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":873817,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ad"},"rt":36520,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":910483,"subject":"THRFC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32007","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 01 PM02 PMX X X J 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8bf"},"rt":2798,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":14925,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c0"},"rt":2142,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":17238,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c1"},"rt":1119,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":18514,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c2"},"rt":1991,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":20671,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c3"},"rt":3083,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24001,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c5"},"rt":1767,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":26776,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c6"},"rt":1094,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":28017,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c7"},"rt":1914,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":30119,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c8"},"rt":1914,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":32201,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8c9"},"rt":1723,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":34085,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ca"},"rt":1367,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":35716,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8cb"},"rt":1516,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":37384,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8cc"},"rt":1732,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":39266,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8cd"},"rt":1501,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":40929,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ce"},"rt":1003,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":42079,"subject":"RBPOL","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e0"},"rt":15876,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":63143,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e1"},"rt":7099,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70358,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e2"},"rt":21475,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91944,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e3"},"rt":114551,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206610,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,H,U","hovered":"04 PME E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e4"},"rt":31995,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238940,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e6"},"rt":9146,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":252642,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e7"},"rt":17110,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":269860,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e8"},"rt":38388,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308363,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7G G B B J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8e9"},"rt":68346,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":376820,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ea"},"rt":37329,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414490,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8eb"},"rt":11439,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":426042,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ec"},"rt":5317,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431475,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ed"},"rt":128995,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":560587,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ee"},"rt":45131,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606042,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f8ef"},"rt":24546,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":630712,"subject":"MHYV3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42360","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f901"},"rt":35268,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98429,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f902"},"rt":8642,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107174,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f903"},"rt":21724,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128994,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f904"},"rt":56229,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185338,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f905"},"rt":48556,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234007,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f907"},"rt":13908,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255460,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f908"},"rt":26114,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281678,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f909"},"rt":33836,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315619,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90a"},"rt":18825,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":334558,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90b"},"rt":62795,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397458,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z C G H Z Z Z O O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90c"},"rt":13400,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411167,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90d"},"rt":8589,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419858,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90e"},"rt":14901,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":434860,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"4Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f90f"},"rt":40901,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":475866,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM09 AM10 AM01 PM02 PM03 PMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f910"},"rt":35738,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":511708,"subject":"5UZCZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37904","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f922"},"rt":30490,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":71263,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"210 AM11 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f923"},"rt":8237,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79777,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f924"},"rt":21778,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":101842,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,Z","hovered":"A Z C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f925"},"rt":14755,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":116877,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM05 PMF U 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f926"},"rt":31962,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149120,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f928"},"rt":8355,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160205,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f929"},"rt":12158,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":172638,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92a"},"rt":26637,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199548,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92b"},"rt":13275,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":213098,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92c"},"rt":22828,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236201,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92d"},"rt":6168,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242654,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92e"},"rt":8179,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251112,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"2X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f92f"},"rt":35920,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":287310,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M F X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f930"},"rt":35861,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323443,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f931"},"rt":19003,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342721,"subject":"COKYH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40761","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f943"},"rt":98869,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168596,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f944"},"rt":19694,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188585,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f945"},"rt":13823,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202516,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f946"},"rt":16246,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218873,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f947"},"rt":33285,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":252342,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f949"},"rt":89884,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":347615,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM01 PM12 PM08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94a"},"rt":54215,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402198,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM05 PM06 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94b"},"rt":50083,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452384,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94c"},"rt":29197,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":481686,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94d"},"rt":9461,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491249,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94e"},"rt":23840,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515217,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f94f"},"rt":15142,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":530500,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f950"},"rt":17674,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":548285,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f951"},"rt":10534,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":558921,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f952"},"rt":15253,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574278,"subject":"UV54H","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44580","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f964"},"rt":21728,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":77949,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f965"},"rt":16587,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":94640,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"6O K E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f966"},"rt":26262,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":121001,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"3C C C C F G U A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f967"},"rt":2307,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":123404,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f968"},"rt":2583,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126083,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96a"},"rt":6502,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":135806,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96b"},"rt":21594,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":157499,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96c"},"rt":2493,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160091,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96d"},"rt":1631,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":161814,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96e"},"rt":1804,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163710,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f96f"},"rt":2368,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":166177,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f970"},"rt":8407,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174679,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f971"},"rt":4090,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":178864,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f972"},"rt":6888,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185849,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f973"},"rt":2181,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188125,"subject":"LNRTX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42553","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f985"},"rt":24826,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69078,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA 01 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f986"},"rt":21731,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":90969,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f987"},"rt":52812,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143946,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 10 AMC C C C U A C C C 10 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f988"},"rt":48887,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193021,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME E E 12 PM09 AMC 08 PM03 PM03 PMX X 10 AM402 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMG 04 PME E E D D G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f989"},"rt":64284,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257485,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,D","hovered":"I I C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f98b"},"rt":9410,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269768,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f98c"},"rt":31353,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301498,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f98d"},"rt":88474,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390164,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f98e"},"rt":23469,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":414469,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f98f"},"rt":41624,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456273,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f990"},"rt":3273,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459703,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f991"},"rt":2628,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462494,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f992"},"rt":1649,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":464361,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f993"},"rt":1664,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466174,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f994"},"rt":3830,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470234,"subject":"U5073","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40794","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9a6"},"rt":92699,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165761,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C C 10 AMA 10 AMA 12 PM11 AMF F F 11 AMF F F F F H A 10 AMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9a7"},"rt":20187,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":186273,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,D","hovered":"2C D D K K D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9a8"},"rt":14992,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":201351,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C O O C 09 AMC C 09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9a9"},"rt":13457,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214895,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"403 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMH H K 05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9aa"},"rt":15850,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230832,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I","hovered":"08 AMI O O O 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ac"},"rt":15021,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":254144,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"P P C E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ad"},"rt":25154,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279384,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I I F F B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ae"},"rt":28976,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308448,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9af"},"rt":34201,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":342737,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B B B B B B M F F F B B M M J J J J 09 AM08 AMI I 0I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b0"},"rt":8088,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350912,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"5E G F F 02 PM02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b1"},"rt":11801,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362801,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b2"},"rt":14882,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377769,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"B B F 10 AMF 10 AMF G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b3"},"rt":20563,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":398417,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMZ Z 01 PMZ 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b4"},"rt":12675,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411185,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PMX X X X X 03 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9b5"},"rt":9266,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420537,"subject":"EX824","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"43328","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"302 PMX 03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9c7"},"rt":19439,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3034984,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9c8"},"rt":14109,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3049175,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9c9"},"rt":10530,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3059792,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ca"},"rt":40997,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3100876,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9cb"},"rt":10747,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3111708,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9cd"},"rt":7979,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":3122143,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ce"},"rt":11767,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3134009,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9cf"},"rt":16229,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3150326,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d0"},"rt":3361,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":3153775,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d1"},"rt":2797,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3156793,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d2"},"rt":583,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3157477,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d3"},"rt":2970,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3160526,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d4"},"rt":15770,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":3176375,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d5"},"rt":15870,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3192326,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9d6"},"rt":8430,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3200843,"subject":"R1DAE","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36723","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9e8"},"rt":8979,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58388,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9e9"},"rt":12184,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":70680,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C Z A A D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ea"},"rt":16121,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86903,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9eb"},"rt":64975,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151977,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM03 PM04 PMU U 04 PM04 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ec"},"rt":47212,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199496,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O I I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ee"},"rt":10341,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":214131,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9ef"},"rt":17418,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231656,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M M B B 4B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f0"},"rt":27829,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259589,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7I I I I B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f1"},"rt":27256,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286953,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f2"},"rt":23324,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310382,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C F F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f3"},"rt":9406,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319907,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f4"},"rt":5456,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325464,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f5"},"rt":38363,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":363935,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X X 03 PM12 PMZ Z X X 3X O X C F Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f6"},"rt":42744,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406793,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631f9f7"},"rt":42256,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449160,"subject":"O9UUF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"33521","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa09"},"rt":14786,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223019,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa0a"},"rt":7156,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230270,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa0b"},"rt":11558,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242152,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa0c"},"rt":25023,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267273,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa0d"},"rt":62111,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329481,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"H H I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa0f"},"rt":12328,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":348077,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"256"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa10"},"rt":30839,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379007,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa11"},"rt":23382,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402496,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"L L B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa12"},"rt":12607,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":415199,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"5J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa13"},"rt":13151,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428449,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"3I B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa14"},"rt":10226,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438788,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa15"},"rt":6851,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445735,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa16"},"rt":41492,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487329,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa17"},"rt":35809,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":523236,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMH 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa18"},"rt":21095,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":544425,"subject":"KBQUZ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa2a"},"rt":17259,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111337,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM02 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa2b"},"rt":10909,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122339,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa2c"},"rt":13296,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135757,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa2d"},"rt":31166,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167010,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PMU U U U U F F F F 03 PM04 PMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa2e"},"rt":100689,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267836,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I O O H H K K H K K U K C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa30"},"rt":7460,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":280860,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa31"},"rt":22495,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303469,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa32"},"rt":45096,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348659,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"M J J I I I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa33"},"rt":22445,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":371197,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa34"},"rt":40824,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412170,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":"F F F F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa35"},"rt":7803,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420076,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa36"},"rt":6918,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427133,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa37"},"rt":54740,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":482027,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"N N N Z O O O O O 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM05 PMM B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa38"},"rt":33013,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515151,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F 03 PM04 PM03 PMZ E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa39"},"rt":51014,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":566261,"subject":"AAAGG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42202","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PMM X M J X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa4b"},"rt":36481,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":103986,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 10 AM11 AMA C A A 11 AM11 AMA C A C C A 11 AM11 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa4c"},"rt":9536,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114300,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa4d"},"rt":26292,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140754,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa4e"},"rt":42128,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183004,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PM04 PMC 11 AMO Z Z 12 PMZ F 01 PMU 03 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa4f"},"rt":111868,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294970,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z A A K O O O I O O O I I O O I O O 10 AM11 AM02 PMU J H H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa51"},"rt":13014,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":315352,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AMI 10 AMI E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa52"},"rt":31733,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347315,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"J X N M J J I B N D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa53"},"rt":61091,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":408534,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F B B B F F F B B B B E 11 AM11 AME E J X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa54"},"rt":25434,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":434446,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4I 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa55"},"rt":68326,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503099,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G,O","hovered":"J M M B B F B B 12 PMM H O O O 01 PM01 PM01 PMM M M 02 PM03 PM03 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMO O O O C C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa56"},"rt":8964,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512435,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa57"},"rt":5333,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517901,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa58"},"rt":29242,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":547315,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,O","hovered":"M M Z Z Z H H H Z Z H Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z 04 PMO 604 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa59"},"rt":16919,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564385,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X 02 PM03 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa5a"},"rt":42905,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607454,"subject":"EOMMH","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44571","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMM 12 PMB B F 12 PM11 AME E 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM09 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa6c"},"rt":32227,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112446,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa6d"},"rt":13001,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125565,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa6e"},"rt":14472,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140146,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa6f"},"rt":19561,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159832,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa70"},"rt":17086,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177033,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa72"},"rt":7813,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190773,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa73"},"rt":26852,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217738,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa74"},"rt":1041,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218892,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa75"},"rt":639,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":219645,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa76"},"rt":568,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220322,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa77"},"rt":11349,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231797,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa78"},"rt":17188,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249114,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa79"},"rt":7123,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256353,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa7a"},"rt":1471,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257936,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa7b"},"rt":326,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258372,"subject":"CSFP5","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44550","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa8d"},"rt":14772,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":57182,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa8e"},"rt":7044,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":64327,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa8f"},"rt":19523,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":84111,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa90"},"rt":34439,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118651,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"12 PM01 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa91"},"rt":7931,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126764,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa93"},"rt":6106,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":136168,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa94"},"rt":36953,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173299,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"53J J J J J J B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa95"},"rt":25953,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199434,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa96"},"rt":37015,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":236621,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J J J M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa97"},"rt":1783,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":238580,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa98"},"rt":7541,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246294,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa99"},"rt":6180,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":252578,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa9a"},"rt":10263,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":262942,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa9b"},"rt":24454,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287497,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AMJ M E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fa9c"},"rt":20954,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":308551,"subject":"9K85Y","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"40782","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faae"},"rt":15902,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":108357,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faaf"},"rt":13697,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122319,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7I I O O F K E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab0"},"rt":20223,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":142728,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"7C C C A 12 PMZ Z A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab1"},"rt":72810,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215719,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A 04 PME E 09 AMC A O O Z Z Z 01 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab2"},"rt":84654,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300699,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I C F F O O 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab4"},"rt":10518,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":318607,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab5"},"rt":23485,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342191,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab6"},"rt":64243,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":406533,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab7"},"rt":32935,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":439795,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab8"},"rt":19858,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459755,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fab9"},"rt":13030,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472890,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faba"},"rt":13548,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486544,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4F B B B F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fabb"},"rt":38694,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":525343,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fabc"},"rt":36466,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561915,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"202 PM03 PM04 PMO O B B B 12 PM01 PMM M 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fabd"},"rt":39869,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":601884,"subject":"GWGDD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42308","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631facf"},"rt":20186,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":73757,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad0"},"rt":8875,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":82930,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad1"},"rt":15719,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98973,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad2"},"rt":38981,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138292,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad3"},"rt":75765,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214378,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad5"},"rt":8315,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229013,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad6"},"rt":18279,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247588,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad7"},"rt":30819,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278785,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad8"},"rt":37060,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":316181,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fad9"},"rt":44057,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360558,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fada"},"rt":9156,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370018,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fadb"},"rt":5445,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375575,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fadc"},"rt":18409,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":394101,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fadd"},"rt":23680,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418128,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fade"},"rt":25468,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443884,"subject":"N2E3Q","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"29388","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf0"},"rt":33016,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141454,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"04 PM03 PMA 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf1"},"rt":11998,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153607,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"2F F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf2"},"rt":15744,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":169509,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"O C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf3"},"rt":11830,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181493,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"U U E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf4"},"rt":46230,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227875,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf6"},"rt":7551,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243865,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf7"},"rt":18073,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262095,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf8"},"rt":52896,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315143,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faf9"},"rt":64151,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":379442,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"2J J J J J P L H 03 PMX M J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fafa"},"rt":60297,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440496,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M C G F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fafb"},"rt":8781,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449680,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AMM 01 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fafc"},"rt":6339,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456171,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fafd"},"rt":21181,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":477508,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fafe"},"rt":69931,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":547582,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM03 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631faff"},"rt":36242,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":584224,"subject":"4KL0G","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44569","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb11"},"rt":17237,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120341,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC A 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb12"},"rt":17091,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137511,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb13"},"rt":43628,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":181212,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C C 02 PMU U U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb14"},"rt":11489,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192787,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"201 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb15"},"rt":21005,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213863,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb17"},"rt":24954,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":245768,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb18"},"rt":25146,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271010,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb19"},"rt":51172,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322266,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"11 AM11 AMB B F G G G A A G G F E F F F X X X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1a"},"rt":14364,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":336705,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1b"},"rt":13281,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350059,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1c"},"rt":15473,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365613,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1d"},"rt":7462,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373148,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1e"},"rt":13780,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387065,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"A Z Z O M F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb1f"},"rt":8804,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":395942,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb20"},"rt":35614,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431627,"subject":"XY039","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"36371","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X K K X X X K K K 11 AM12 PM01 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb32"},"rt":17248,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":88334,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM09 AM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb33"},"rt":9327,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97765,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb34"},"rt":24747,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":122620,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb35"},"rt":16250,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138966,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb36"},"rt":35330,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174399,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb38"},"rt":7217,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185533,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb39"},"rt":36379,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":222016,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3a"},"rt":18189,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240633,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3b"},"rt":15078,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255815,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3c"},"rt":9138,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265065,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3d"},"rt":7189,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":272349,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3e"},"rt":9264,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281716,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb3f"},"rt":18695,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":300516,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":"G L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb40"},"rt":11264,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311882,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I,O","hovered":"G C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb41"},"rt":14668,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":326651,"subject":"Y2AE1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"31365","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb53"},"rt":5961,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":24710,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb54"},"rt":54243,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":79041,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb55"},"rt":10536,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89666,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"F 10 AMC A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb56"},"rt":7948,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":97704,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"H B 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb57"},"rt":165967,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":263765,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I U U 02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM02 PM04 PM07 PMI I 03 PM03 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb59"},"rt":37101,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":304474,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5a"},"rt":18405,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322982,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5b"},"rt":22476,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345547,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5c"},"rt":10634,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356281,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5d"},"rt":112167,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468537,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F B B B F F B Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5e"},"rt":16060,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":484915,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb5f"},"rt":7926,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":492928,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb60"},"rt":23798,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":516814,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"B B Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb61"},"rt":15666,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532566,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I 03 PM03 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb62"},"rt":11595,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":544248,"subject":"RYKV8","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44596","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb74"},"rt":39643,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114895,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb75"},"rt":16408,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131401,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMF O O E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb76"},"rt":20115,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":151624,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C Z 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb77"},"rt":153557,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305296,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z Z F F O O K K 02 PMU U 10 AMH 01 PMH H D D 04 PM04 PMZ F 01 PMF F F 12 PMF F F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb78"},"rt":146781,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452375,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,U","hovered":"O 06 PM07 PM05 PM04 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7a"},"rt":11109,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":468408,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7b"},"rt":29246,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":497750,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7c"},"rt":75925,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573765,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.4166666666666665,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":5,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E,I,J,N,Z","hovered":"G B X 02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7d"},"rt":79611,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":653757,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B B B J J 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMB B I 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7e"},"rt":57601,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":711664,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AMG G G G G M M X 02 PM02 PMX E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb7f"},"rt":12450,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":724226,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PMB B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb80"},"rt":10555,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":734886,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F X X B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb81"},"rt":22462,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":757442,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"D Z Z 04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb82"},"rt":54049,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":811591,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X O O X M 12 PMM M X O O B 12 PM12 PM2B I J F F F E E 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb83"},"rt":132299,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":943979,"subject":"YS1XM","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44084","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"08 AM12 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb95"},"rt":12607,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":59064,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb96"},"rt":21614,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":80761,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"Z Z A C B E D E E 5E 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb97"},"rt":17152,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":98000,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C A A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb98"},"rt":67639,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":165720,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"05 PMO K K E Z A C A U U A A F F O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb99"},"rt":53301,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219264,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I O I I I H I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb9b"},"rt":9817,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233648,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb9c"},"rt":28248,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261976,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J N X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb9d"},"rt":23054,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285160,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I F H H Z Z L L X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb9e"},"rt":16846,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":302088,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"G B B J J I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fb9f"},"rt":27808,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329977,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fba0"},"rt":9863,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339920,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fba1"},"rt":5727,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345728,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fba2"},"rt":39976,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385784,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"G Z Z Z O X X M M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fba3"},"rt":45770,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431640,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMB 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fba4"},"rt":12238,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443960,"subject":"OKOOU","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44453","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbb6"},"rt":20230,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100204,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A 11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbb7"},"rt":10765,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111523,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbb8"},"rt":48452,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":160086,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PM12 PMC 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PMZ A 06 PM06 PM06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbb9"},"rt":13639,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173827,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PM01 PM03 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbba"},"rt":15299,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":189227,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"02 PM02 PMI I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbbc"},"rt":21519,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":217948,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"12 PME E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbbd"},"rt":12687,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":230731,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbbe"},"rt":35149,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265979,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F B B B F F B X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbbf"},"rt":26114,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":292187,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I 10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc0"},"rt":33104,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325387,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I F F 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc1"},"rt":7839,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333323,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc2"},"rt":6081,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":339499,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc3"},"rt":39092,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":378691,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"11 AM12 PMZ 04 PMZ X X X B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc4"},"rt":31808,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410603,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbc5"},"rt":60602,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471299,"subject":"8PO0A","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41157","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X J M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbd7"},"rt":13446,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":68101,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A A 33"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbd8"},"rt":7498,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":75714,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbd9"},"rt":10429,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86306,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbda"},"rt":16749,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":103160,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6O F F 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbdb"},"rt":49914,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":153178,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"O I G G G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbdd"},"rt":11552,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":181476,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbde"},"rt":17593,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":199195,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbdf"},"rt":19332,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":218620,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe0"},"rt":11109,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":229822,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe1"},"rt":14979,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244914,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe2"},"rt":9032,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":254049,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,H","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe3"},"rt":8141,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262287,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"G C C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe4"},"rt":12733,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275112,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe5"},"rt":31736,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306951,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"5X M M M B X X X M J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbe6"},"rt":21935,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328983,"subject":"ZTWPC","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G","hovered":"601 PMM M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbf8"},"rt":23002,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89827,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbf9"},"rt":9081,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":99242,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbfa"},"rt":10995,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":110574,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbfb"},"rt":9404,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120274,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbfc"},"rt":27609,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148140,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O I I O O 06 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbfe"},"rt":16837,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":170344,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fbff"},"rt":4261,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":174890,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc00"},"rt":2402,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":177659,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc01"},"rt":2785,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180825,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc02"},"rt":2215,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":183407,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc03"},"rt":1770,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185457,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc04"},"rt":2895,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188607,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc05"},"rt":1111,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190090,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc06"},"rt":4688,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195407,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc07"},"rt":3218,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198957,"subject":"GXPXV","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"32287","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc19"},"rt":32366,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66161,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc1a"},"rt":11902,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78146,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc1b"},"rt":13723,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":91949,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc1c"},"rt":17002,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109037,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc1d"},"rt":1971,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":111087,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc1f"},"rt":3071,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":116825,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc20"},"rt":1718,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118622,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc21"},"rt":1753,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":120456,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc22"},"rt":1669,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":122206,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc23"},"rt":1769,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":124057,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc24"},"rt":1370,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":125507,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc25"},"rt":2920,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128509,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc26"},"rt":17123,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":145713,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc27"},"rt":13140,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158933,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc28"},"rt":2502,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161516,"subject":"V4BAX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"41204","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc3a"},"rt":35558,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":107573,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A 11 AMA A 10 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc3b"},"rt":54179,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":161859,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PM02 PMD E E D G G G D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc3c"},"rt":51315,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":213281,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"A C C C C I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc3d"},"rt":14296,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227684,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc3e"},"rt":14326,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242121,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc40"},"rt":10926,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":260819,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc41"},"rt":24420,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285355,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc42"},"rt":62237,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347694,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X X B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc43"},"rt":17778,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":365799,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc44"},"rt":8325,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374229,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc45"},"rt":9385,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383714,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc46"},"rt":18246,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402070,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F B B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc47"},"rt":14057,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":416235,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc48"},"rt":8740,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425085,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"008 AM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc49"},"rt":23227,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448425,"subject":"TNQQA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"40483","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"12 PM01 PMX X 02 PM02 PM03 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc5b"},"rt":15024,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78725,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc5c"},"rt":10530,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89580,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I H E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc5d"},"rt":19135,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":109041,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"I A A C C C C C A Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc5e"},"rt":40783,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150139,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"K A C Z C A A A Z F O O O O O I H H H H H H H J J U U 34"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc5f"},"rt":61690,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212108,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"H K I I I O I I O O 02 PM03 PM04 PMU Z A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc61"},"rt":8141,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":225843,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"Z 79E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc62"},"rt":23555,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249691,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc63"},"rt":24728,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274707,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B B E N Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc64"},"rt":28462,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":303523,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"O J 09 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMI J J I I M M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc65"},"rt":31874,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335683,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"8F 12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM04 PMM M J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc66"},"rt":14038,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350025,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"N O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc67"},"rt":7295,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357603,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc68"},"rt":28928,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":386812,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 04 PMZ 5X X B B M C C F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc69"},"rt":17082,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404184,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc6a"},"rt":46409,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":450885,"subject":"27JZD","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"41452","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMF 11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM7B O C E E F B B 01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc7c"},"rt":88391,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248960,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6C C 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB 04 PMC I O 11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMC C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc7d"},"rt":60933,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310568,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F D D 01 PMU U K D 12 PMD C 09 AM09 AM10 AMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc7e"},"rt":11637,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323132,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc7f"},"rt":11768,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335020,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc80"},"rt":18375,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353519,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc82"},"rt":10826,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":374944,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc83"},"rt":30098,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405161,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"75"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc84"},"rt":50012,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455296,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"9C C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc85"},"rt":32868,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":488282,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc86"},"rt":15318,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503720,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc87"},"rt":10577,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514417,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"09 AM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc88"},"rt":9758,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524289,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc89"},"rt":38897,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":563306,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"Z 02 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc8a"},"rt":22988,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":586409,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM04 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc8b"},"rt":36206,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622732,"subject":"N1XCQ","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44615","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"401 PMF 03 PM03 PMX 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc9d"},"rt":16779,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":60414,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6A 12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AMA C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc9e"},"rt":15604,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":76103,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B B D D D E E Z A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fc9f"},"rt":56490,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132679,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"01 PMU H J J A A A A A X X U Z C C C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca0"},"rt":31688,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164458,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"406 PM05 PM04 PM04 PMU U F O O Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca1"},"rt":338932,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":503473,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I I I I I 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca3"},"rt":13744,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":525381,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AMG E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca4"},"rt":25165,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550627,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca5"},"rt":46456,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":597165,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6B B J J J B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca6"},"rt":24310,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":621555,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B J J I I I I 10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca7"},"rt":74019,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":695656,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B O C C C X B B F 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMZ 04 PMX X X X B 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMB B F B B F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMF F E 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca8"},"rt":8085,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704055,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fca9"},"rt":7894,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":712032,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcaa"},"rt":29134,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":741250,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X X M Z F 3X J J J I E 11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcab"},"rt":26016,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":767346,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMM M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcac"},"rt":59110,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":826538,"subject":"06PK3","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44412","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3I O B 02 PM02 PM02 PM11 AM01 PM02 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMF F B 01 PM02 PMF B F F B F F I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcbe"},"rt":27346,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346714,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcbf"},"rt":16953,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":363782,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U F K E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc0"},"rt":22018,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386020,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc1"},"rt":98462,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":484600,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc2"},"rt":115045,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600162,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc4"},"rt":15616,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":625626,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc5"},"rt":52935,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678675,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc6"},"rt":54008,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":732818,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc7"},"rt":45621,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":778564,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc8"},"rt":57500,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":836176,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcc9"},"rt":24662,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":860957,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcca"},"rt":12660,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":873732,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fccb"},"rt":46995,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":920847,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fccc"},"rt":31912,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":952933,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fccd"},"rt":78016,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1031074,"subject":"PY3S1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"36404","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcdf"},"rt":59382,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":154486,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMA 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce0"},"rt":9293,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163881,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce1"},"rt":18186,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182165,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce2"},"rt":39077,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221359,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C 02 PM03 PMK K K U U H H J O F F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce3"},"rt":114357,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335819,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I K Z Z H H O U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce5"},"rt":10697,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352652,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce6"},"rt":12593,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365348,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce7"},"rt":53129,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418579,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce8"},"rt":39444,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":458125,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"H H X J J J J I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fce9"},"rt":43142,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":501372,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"K P P J B F F F B B Z O X X X B E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcea"},"rt":11655,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513130,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fceb"},"rt":6476,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":519709,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcec"},"rt":25953,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":545764,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O H Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fced"},"rt":23463,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":569331,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X X X M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fcee"},"rt":33590,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603021,"subject":"GBLLF","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44609","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F 4E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd00"},"rt":41214,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126307,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A 11 AMA 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd01"},"rt":21746,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148155,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C K K 03 PMC 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd02"},"rt":14546,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162798,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd03"},"rt":45244,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208141,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"Z 12 PMC A O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd04"},"rt":28135,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":236373,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd06"},"rt":8735,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":255477,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd07"},"rt":43142,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298716,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.41666666666666663,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":5,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,D,F,I,J,N,O,Z,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd08"},"rt":33651,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332474,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.6666666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F,G,H,Z","hovered":"G G F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd09"},"rt":109560,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442136,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0a"},"rt":13991,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456397,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0b"},"rt":13320,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":469813,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AMB 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0c"},"rt":19751,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":489655,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0d"},"rt":23021,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":512765,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0e"},"rt":9284,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":522130,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd0f"},"rt":3416,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525635,"subject":"XAVGA","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"31354","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd21"},"rt":24621,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":118980,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA 11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd22"},"rt":18582,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":137693,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A K D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd23"},"rt":25039,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162849,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd24"},"rt":118391,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281350,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"008 AM09 AM04 PMU U H H Z Z F F K K O K O F F 11 AM11 AM10 AMC C C 01 PMF F F F F U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd25"},"rt":80217,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361937,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"4I I O O A A I I I I U O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd27"},"rt":16196,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388575,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd28"},"rt":19708,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":408399,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM10 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd29"},"rt":124983,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":533487,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B J B E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2a"},"rt":34827,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":568843,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2b"},"rt":55220,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":624179,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"2F Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2c"},"rt":11042,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":635423,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2d"},"rt":15764,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":651342,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2e"},"rt":29162,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":680749,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"I Z O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd2f"},"rt":63932,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":744805,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"103 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd30"},"rt":55393,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":800628,"subject":"26S2T","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42589","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd42"},"rt":25733,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":86535,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd43"},"rt":9122,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":95743,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd44"},"rt":16942,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":112767,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd45"},"rt":60438,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173288,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"E E E E 04 PM04 PMK H H H I A 11 AMZ 04 PME E D D D E K H U U U U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd46"},"rt":79828,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253448,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"12 PMI I 03 PMI 11 AM11 AM02 PMU Z A F 12 PM12 PM01 PMH F H I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd48"},"rt":12888,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275153,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd49"},"rt":21634,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296872,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4a"},"rt":41101,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338056,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4b"},"rt":40171,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":378312,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4c"},"rt":30821,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":409216,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F C 04 PMN X O O B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4d"},"rt":8822,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418120,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4e"},"rt":4935,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423136,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd4f"},"rt":67677,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490897,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X J J O O X X D N O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd50"},"rt":26775,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517922,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F 05 PM04 PM03 PMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd51"},"rt":50310,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":568314,"subject":"1F3SX","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"39097","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PMM B B F F X F E E G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd63"},"rt":38831,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":114002,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"312 PM12 PMA A A 11 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd64"},"rt":8967,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":123071,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D D A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd65"},"rt":20484,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":143655,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd66"},"rt":15506,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":159259,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"01 PM02 PM05 PMU A A A A 10 AM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd67"},"rt":13802,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173163,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd69"},"rt":5794,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":184219,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6a"},"rt":13541,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":197861,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6b"},"rt":51982,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249941,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6c"},"rt":22937,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":272986,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I I J I E E F F M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6d"},"rt":5359,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278474,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6e"},"rt":7366,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285941,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd6f"},"rt":8282,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294325,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd70"},"rt":12504,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":306933,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J Z Z J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd71"},"rt":6009,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313047,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M 03 PMI 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd72"},"rt":11926,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325076,"subject":"2TZNG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44526","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd84"},"rt":20007,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2485592,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd85"},"rt":16450,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2502149,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd86"},"rt":15468,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2517734,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd87"},"rt":24023,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2541867,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd88"},"rt":81067,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2623048,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8a"},"rt":9704,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2644313,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8b"},"rt":26291,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2670710,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8c"},"rt":100964,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2771803,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8d"},"rt":25912,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2798072,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8e"},"rt":101570,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2899755,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O F F F F Z 04 PMI B B X X G O O X C G G C B L H H 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd8f"},"rt":12714,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2912784,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd90"},"rt":14560,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2927446,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd91"},"rt":48714,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2976376,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B B B Z Z F J X O I G B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd92"},"rt":66239,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3042720,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM11 AMM 04 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fd93"},"rt":58205,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":3101210,"subject":"HTMPG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"37875","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMX X B 08 AMM M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fda5"},"rt":47041,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198205,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"10 AM08 AMC 11 AM12 PM11 AMA 11 AMA A A A A 11 AMC C 11 AM12 PM11 AMZ F A U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fda6"},"rt":9857,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208163,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"1D K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fda7"},"rt":147010,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355275,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"4C A 11 AMC A 12 PM12 PM01 PMU U U U C A 11 AM12 PM01 PMU U U U U U 01 PMU E U 07 PM08 PM07 PM05 PM04 PM12 PM11 AMC C C C C C 09 AMC 09 AMC 11 AMZ Z A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fda8"},"rt":27125,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382686,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"11 AM12 PMH H H 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fda9"},"rt":98577,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481512,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdab"},"rt":11189,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":498129,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdac"},"rt":33620,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531850,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"N D D 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PMX X X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdad"},"rt":71466,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":603412,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7F B B B B 11 AMB B B B B B B B B B C F F B C 04 PMF G G F F F E F 22"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdae"},"rt":17272,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":620979,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdaf"},"rt":17769,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":638849,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F B B 02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdb0"},"rt":14135,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":653081,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdb1"},"rt":10662,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":663842,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdb2"},"rt":9113,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":673052,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdb3"},"rt":8267,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":681428,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdb4"},"rt":69851,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":751372,"subject":"PMSG1","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"44611","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PMX X X 09 AM10 AMF G 02 PM12 PM02 PMX 2M G G C C X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdc6"},"rt":29179,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":100800,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM11 AMA A A 11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A A A A A A A A A C A 11 AM10 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdc7"},"rt":18923,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119796,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E D E 04 PM04 PMH E E D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdc8"},"rt":9410,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":129282,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3C C A Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdc9"},"rt":60965,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190318,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"5Z F U 04 PM04 PM04 PMH H H 01 PM02 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMU U I O O O O O 12 PMU U J F U U U U U F U U 02 PM12 PMZ Z A 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdca"},"rt":71501,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262100,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"11 AMZ Z I I I O 03 PM01 PM02 PM05 PM05 PM03 PMK K H H H 01 PM02 PM03 PMU F F F O O O O O O O U U H J H I I F G B G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdcc"},"rt":13207,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":280082,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E G E B D X J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdcd"},"rt":25372,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305537,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F B B B F F B B B B B I 3F B B B B N L L G G J N D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdce"},"rt":35363,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":340971,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F F B B E F F B B X X X B B I I B B E E G J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdcf"},"rt":24644,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":365684,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J J J I I I I I B B J J J H Z N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd0"},"rt":44926,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410680,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F F B B 12 PMB B 03 PM04 PMZ Z Z X X X 04 PMM C H C E G G 11 AMG G A A A A I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd1"},"rt":16803,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427554,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"110 AM02 PM12 PMM M F 01 PMM 12 PMB F F 02 PM12 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd2"},"rt":8158,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435783,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd3"},"rt":22922,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":458775,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"I B Z Z Z X X X 3X N E G C C 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd4"},"rt":38002,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496847,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMX X 03 PMB O B 01 PMF F F 11 AMJ A X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdd5"},"rt":38291,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535210,"subject":"4QXNS","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"37884","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AM03 PM02 PMX X X X F F 02 PMG G X 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fde7"},"rt":45801,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231102,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fde8"},"rt":18716,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249914,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fde9"},"rt":24397,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274409,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C Z Z C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdea"},"rt":82604,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357106,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K U U 12 PMZ U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdeb"},"rt":252872,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610247,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O 11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fded"},"rt":19307,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":639765,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdee"},"rt":47389,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":687251,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdef"},"rt":68640,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":755983,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf0"},"rt":34298,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":790620,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf1"},"rt":98062,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":888773,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf2"},"rt":24397,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":913437,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf3"},"rt":12942,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":926466,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf4"},"rt":50983,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":977543,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf5"},"rt":64912,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1042547,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fdf6"},"rt":89615,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1132422,"subject":"MVRRG","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"42484","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMX 02 PM02 PMB B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe08"},"rt":30920,"condition":"114","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":89288,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O 11 AMA A A A A A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe09"},"rt":36928,"condition":"114","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126328,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PM01 PMZ E D E E 05 PMG D D D E E 04 PM05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe0a"},"rt":40846,"condition":"114","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":167279,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe0b"},"rt":98589,"condition":"114","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265974,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe0c"},"rt":36131,"condition":"114","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302424,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe0e"},"rt":9328,"condition":"114","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":316511,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe0f"},"rt":39721,"condition":"114","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356336,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B B F F F B B B B F F F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe10"},"rt":160748,"condition":"114","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517193,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"8B O G 01 PMM M M G E F F B B 56X X X X X J J X 04 PMH I I I J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe11"},"rt":41571,"condition":"114","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":559070,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B J I I B B B I 09 AMI B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe12"},"rt":108093,"condition":"114","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":667272,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F B B B B F F F F B B B F F 04 PM04 PM03 PMM B B B X X X X 02 PM02 PMX 10 AM11 AMM M O C 10 AM11 AMF F A A 08 AM09 AM10 AM10 AMI J J B B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe13"},"rt":23075,"condition":"114","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":690677,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM11 AM02 PM12 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe14"},"rt":17922,"condition":"114","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":708709,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F B 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe15"},"rt":63118,"condition":"114","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":771966,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3X X Z 04 PM04 PMZ Z Z 01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMF 5J X X X O F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe16"},"rt":52033,"condition":"114","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":824308,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F M 4I E E A M M X O N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe17"},"rt":132023,"condition":"114","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"4","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":956442,"subject":"UC548","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"35137","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F X X X F F F F B M M E E 11 AM11 AMF F F F B B K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe29"},"rt":30504,"condition":"115","q":1,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":197986,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A Z 12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe2a"},"rt":16107,"condition":"115","q":2,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214177,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E O E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe2b"},"rt":19852,"condition":"115","q":3,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234116,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A 09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe2c"},"rt":88300,"condition":"115","q":4,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322500,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O 12 PMZ Z Z Z 01 PM01 PM12 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe2d"},"rt":190462,"condition":"115","q":5,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":513203,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I C C C C I I I I I O O 12 PM12 PM12 PM02 PM02 PM03 PMG G G B B B E E D 03 PMI 11 AM12 PMU U U K K H H J J H 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe2f"},"rt":25409,"condition":"115","q":6,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":549620,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H H E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe30"},"rt":26658,"condition":"115","q":7,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":576362,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6F F B B M M O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe31"},"rt":54735,"condition":"115","q":8,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":631177,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe32"},"rt":117294,"condition":"115","q":9,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":748553,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"6J J 09 AM10 AMI I I B J J J J 09 AM09 AMI I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe33"},"rt":65874,"condition":"115","q":10,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":814664,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PMF Z C C H C G G E G Z Z 04 PMZ X F O O O B M M J X X X Z X 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe34"},"rt":6311,"condition":"115","q":11,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":821295,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe35"},"rt":6872,"condition":"115","q":12,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":828255,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe36"},"rt":21358,"condition":"115","q":13,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":849695,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3Z Z Z Z F F Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe37"},"rt":79351,"condition":"115","q":14,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":929127,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J J 03 PMH G G C Z Z O X B 12 PMB B B I I I 06 PM05 PM04 PMX B O 03 PMB B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"630523de6f72b3ed8631fe38"},"rt":95964,"condition":"115","q":15,"explicit":1,"impasse":1,"grid":"5","mark":"","ixn":1,"rotation":"","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1025398,"subject":"M12WR","study":"SGC4A","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2217","sona_id":"44625","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M C E G X X X E E G X X F X X B B 02 PMI 3X I I I I "}]
